<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JEJAKKAKI</string>
    <!-- TODO: Hapus atau ubah teks placeholder ini -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="info">INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="tumbuhan">PLANTS</string>
    <string name="keanekaragaman_hayati">BIODIVERSITY</string>
    <string name="hewan">ANIMAL \n&amp; \nPLANTS</string>
    <string name="aktifitas">ACTIVITY</string>
    <string name="rute">ROUTE</string>
    <string name="taman_nasional">NATIONAL PARK</string>
    <string name="lowcase_taman_nasional">National Park</string>
    <string name="taman_info1">
        Stepping out of our usual track, Tangkahan ecotourism in Batang Serangan Langkat, North Sumatra, beckons. A hidden paradise, part of Gunung Leuser National Park, it boasts a forest patrol team led by elephants and their trainers, the Srati. Visitors can join their noble endeavor, a journey that spans days deep into the forest, from Tangkahan to Bukit Lawang.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info2">
        Named after the Batang Gadis River, this national park harbors crucial wildlife displaced by habitat destruction from land clearing and fires. Stretching along the Bukit Barisan mountain range, it ranges from 300 to 2,145 meters above sea level, with Mount Sorik Marapi as its highest peak. It serves as a vital sanctuary for the region\'s diverse flora and fauna.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info3">
        In 2004, the area became a national park, spanning 38,000 hectares. By 2009, it expanded to 83,000 hectares, a move reflecting its emerald-like richness in tropical biodiversity. Nestled in Sumatra\'s rainforest, this park embodies ecological significance, making the expansion a fitting decision, preserving its vibrant ecosystems for generations to come.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info4">
        Siberut National Park, one of Indonesia\'s ten Biosphere Reserves, lies in Mentawai Island, West Sumatera, 155 km from Padang, the province\'s capital. Sixty percent of its area is primary forest, including Dipterocarpacear and mixed primary forests, swamps, coastal, and mangrove forests. This park has a natural forest with a canopy rising as high as 60 meters.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info5">
        Nestled within the mist of Kerinci Seblat National Park, the enigmatic Kerinci summit remains veiled by ethereal fog, its allure captivating countless adventurers. Enshrouded in mystery, this active mountain\'s summit, adorned with sub-alpine flora, beckons seekers of nature\'s secrets to unravel its majestic heights and delve into the beauty of its terrain.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info6">
        Nestled within the asylum area of 60,500 hectares across Sarolangun, Bungo Tebo, and Batang districts, Bukit Duabelas, aptly named for its 12 main hills, now extends its allure beyond mere landscape. Its enchanting vistas unveil a tapestry of unique natural scenery, offering a sanctuary where nature\'s splendor unfolds in harmonious symphony with the land.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info7">
        Bukit Tigapuluh National Park lies amidst Sumatera\'s lowland, distinct from the Bukit Barisan ridge to its west. Exploring it reveals tropical humidity, inducing sweat. The park boasts four ecosystems: pristine forest, logged-over areas, bushes, rubber plantations, and fields. It\'s a landscape teeming with life, nestled in the heart of Sumatera\'s terrain.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info89">
        Berbak National Park, the largest wetland conservation area in Southeast Asia, stores the largest carbon in the world. On the other hand, Sembilang National Park on Sumatra Island  is a haven for thousands of East Asian and Australian migratory birds, including peat swamp forests and riparian forests. Both parks are essential for environmental conservation.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info10">
        Located at the southern line of Bukit Barisan mountains, Bukit Barisan Selatan National  Park is a home for large mammals such as Sumatran tigers (Panthera tigris sumatrensis), Sumatran elephants (Elephas maximus sumatranus) and Sumatran rhinos (Dicerorhinus  sumatrensis). This place not only shelters these iconic species but also fosters rich biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info11">
        Way Kambas National Park was drawn attention from the world after the birth of Andatu in 2012. This baby Sumatran Rhinoceros (Dicerorhinus sumatraensis) has given a triumph for the park. A hard effort has delivered to support a semi-in-situ captive of Way Kambas\' Sumatran Rhino Sanctuary. Literally, Andatu stands for \'Anugerah dari Tuhan\' meaning Gift from God.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info12">
        Gunung Palung National Park is the only Dipterocarpaceae tropical rain forest which is   considered to be the best and widest forest in Kalimantan island. This forest cover is a chain of hills and significantly important as a water resource for the locals. The park\'s topography varies from lowland to highland, with two mountain summits in the middle.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info13">
        Bentarum National Park in West Kalimantan is the largest conservation area in the region. Known for its contrasting rainy and dry seasons, it includes Lake Sentarum and Betung Kerihun. The park offers diverse ecosystems: lowland, swamp, old secondary, and Dipterocarpus forests. It houses 75% of Kalimantan\'s endemic plants, making it vital for the biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info14">
        Bukit Baka - Bukit Raya National Park may sound a little unique. This park is a combination of two national nature reserves of thetwo provinces, namely Bukit Baka Nature Reserve in West Kalimantan, and Bukit Raya Nature Reserve in Central Kalimantan. The  biodiversity of Bukit Baka - Bukit Raya is also abundant: 817 plant species out of  139 families.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info16">
        Borneo Orangutan (Pongo pygmaeus) Rehabilitation Center in Camp Leaky has been the main tourist attraction in Tanjung Puting National Park,Pangkalan Bun, Kotawaringin Barat, Central Kalimantan. The research center was builtin the 1970s. The highlight is the feeding time of the Asian great ape, the Orangutan, where tourists can observe these creatures up close.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info17">
        Sebangau National Park is a representative of swamp peat forest ecosystem di Central Kalimantan that supports three watercatchment area; Sebangau, Kahayan, and Katingan. The park maintains and cares of these catchment areas and supports the life of human and  wildlife. The local tribe rely their transportation mobility on the rivers flowing in the park.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info18">
        Just like Betung Kerihun National Park, Kayan Mentarang National Park is also located  adjacent to the neighbouring country, Malaysia at two points ;Sarawak on the west and   Sabah the north. Located at the border of Indonesia and Malaysia serves this park as a   fort to the nation in term of sovereignty as well as the sustainability of its natural   resources.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info19">
        Bunaken, a diver\'s paradise globally acclaimed, is a cherished marine destination in Indonesia. Situated within Bunaken National Park, North Sulawesi. Alongside Manado Tua, Mantehage, Siladen, and Nain, it forms the park\'s picturesque landscape. Accessible within a swift 45-minute boat ride from Manado, it entices enthusiasts with its underwater wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info20">
        A very distinctive karst landscape stands as natural sculptures in the Bantimurung   Bulusaraung National Park, Maros, South Sulawesi. No wonder it is often called as a   karst tower. Because, It is standing tall with sharp fractures. Karst formation in Maros  is recognized as the second largest karst landscape while the first is in southern China.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info21">
        Dozens taka, Bungin, and the islands forms the landscape of Taka Bonerate. String of    small islands, and the lagoon from the sand sediment, broken coral and shells form the younger soils. The word of Taka Bonerate itself means reef on the sand. The region  once known as tiger atolls (tiger land) comprising of store barrier reef, fringing reef and ring reef.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info22">
        Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park sprawls from South East Sulawesi\'s tip, safeguarding Wallacea\'s wetland ecosystem. Spanning 105.194 hectares, it acts as a colossal water catchment for the island, crucial for sustaining life. Recognized as a World Ramsar Site, this park bears significant responsibility in preserving biodiversity and ecological balance.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info23">
        In the vibrant heart of the Coral Triangle lies Wakatobi, a miniature archipelago. Bathed in sunlight, Wakatobi National Park, nestled in Southeast Sulawesi, inviting travelers to its piers. Its name, Wakatobi, derived from its islands: Wangi-Wangi, Kaledupa, Tomia, and Binongko, offers an invitation to explore the wonders of this marine sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info24">
        Lore Lindu National Park in Indonesia is a captivating blend of biodiversity and cultural heritage. Nestled in Wallacea, it showcases endemic species alongside ancient Megalithicum sites, making it unique. With a sprawling 217 hectares, the park\'s landscapes vary from 300 to 2,610 meters above sea level, boasting the majestic Mount Tokosa. It\'s a wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info25">
        Kepulauan Togean, nestled in Central Sulawesi, is a marine national park, its small islands harboring rich biodiversity, including endemic species. Sheltered within the Gulf of Tomini, it\'s a small islands surrounded by reef coral. This park is included in the World Coral Triangle or the Coral Triangle, so this national park is very important to be proteced.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info26">
        In North Sulawesi, beyond Bunaken National Park lies another gem: Bogani Nani Warta Bone National Park, nestled just three hours from Manado precisely in Kotamobagu. This sanctuary safeguards endangered species like the Maleo birds (Macrocephalon maleo) and lowland Anoa, showcasing the region\'s rich biodiversity and commitment to conservation efforts.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info27">
        Bunaken is known worldwide as a paradise for diving lovers. The island has also been one of the favourite marine tourist destinations in the country. Bunaken island is a part of Bunaken National Park, located in Manado, North Sulawesi. Manado Tua, Mantehage, Siladen, and Nain are other main islands landscaping the park. Bunaken is easily accessed fromManado.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info28">
        This National park, lying on the western edge of Java, is very challenging to see the Javan rhino at first hand (Rhinoceros sondaicus). Although they only have limited spread areas in Cikeusik and Citadahan, it is always a thrilling challenge to watch one-horned animals from Ranggon, atop a 5 – 7 meters height bamboo stage, amidst the lush wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info29">
        Oasis in the desert. That nickname is appropriate for Kepulauan Seribu National Park. A natural white sandy island and a great underwater world offer a piece of paradise for travelers. Given the fact that the location is near to Jakarta, Kepulauan Seribu deserves to make a perfect vacation on the weekend. Underwater beauty anticipates you to enjoy.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info30">
        This national park asserts itself as the largest tropical mountain rainforest remaining on the island of Java. This area is covered with wallowed germplasms of natural forest. The dense forest of Halimun is inhabited by rare primates: Javan gibbon (Hylobates moloch) and Surili (Presbytis comata).
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info31">
        Who doesn\'t know Gunung Gede Pangrango National Park? The ease of its accessibility makes it easier for visitors from Jakarta, Bogor, Sukabumi coming to the park. An impression of a romantic voyage generally said by visitors after spending their time exploring the park, surrounded by breathtaking vistas, diverse wildlife, lush greenery, and tranquil streams.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info32">
        Mount Ciremai last erupted in 1938. Its beautiful looks include undulating hills and a conical summit. Rising to 3,078 meters above sea level, it\'s surrounded by rice terraces, cold air, and clear rivers. Spanning 15,500 hectares, the park serves as a crucial water reservoir, feeding 43 rivers and 156 springs, with 147 providing year-round drinking water.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info33">
        Off Central Java\'s coast, the Java Sea reefs lie peacefully in Karimunjawa Islands. Besides Kepulauan Seribu in Jakarta, this park offers an excellent opportunity for divers with unimaginable coral reefs. Divers can explore up to 20 feet deep around Small Menjangan, Cemara Besar, and Tengah Island. Discover the underwater beauty in this serene area.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info34">
        Nine craters from the Mount Merbabu eruption have become significant geological phenomena in Central Java. Gunung Merbabu National Park, with its two summits, preserves geological materials, including loose debris and solidified lava. Merbabu is ideal for those who wish to climb to the summit while observing geological processes from hundreds of years ago.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info35">
        Towering on the northern horizon, Mount Merapi stands as a landmark of Yogyakarta\'s landscape and culture. Known for its intense activity, it is among the world\'s 16 most active volcanoes. Its magnetic charm attracts climbers, adventurers, and nature lovers. Each time it erupts, it draws the attention of volcanologists, geologists, and researchers worldwide.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info36">
Usually, watching the crater of the mountain closely to the steep trail must trace all odds of nature. Tourists can easily reach Bromo crater rim without such struggles. The crater lies within Bromo Tengger Semeru National Park. Visitors are crossing the sandy ocean towards the crater either on foot, by jeep or riding horses just like a cowboy horseback.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info37">
        The landscape in southern East Java serves as a final refuge for diverse flora and fauna. Meru Betiri, bordering the Indian Ocean, hosts four of seven sea turtle species. Green turtle, Hawksbill (Eretmochelys imbricata), slengkrah (Lepidochelys olivacea), and  Leatherback turtle (Dermochelys coriacea) visited the coastal of Meru Betiri to bury their eggs.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info38">
        Baluran National Park in Situbondo, East Java, boasts a mesmerizing landscape resembling a slice of the African savanna. Its vast grasslands and scattered acacia trees create an enchanting ambiance. Baluran\'s nickname, "the tiny African of Java," reflects its remarkable resemblance to the African wilderness, captivating visitors\' imagination and hearts.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info39">
        Alas Purwo transcends being just wilderness; it embodies a profound connection with the cultural and religious fabric of the locals. Situated in Banyuwangi, East Java, Alas Purwo National Park is revered as more than mere land; it\'s a sanctuary for wanderers, seekers, spiritual pilgrims, nature fans, adventurers, ecologists, and conservationists alike.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info40">
        White cotton fluffy mixed with lovely blue streaks around the eyes. This is how Bali starling which is naturally living only in Bali looks like. British ornithologist Baron Stressmann discovered Leucopsar rothschildi on March 24, 1911. The Maluku Ship Expedition II, carrying researchers, made the discovery. The ship was ashore in Singaraja for three months.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info41">
        In the past, Mount Rinjani reached 5,000 meters above sea level. Now, at 3,726 meters, its summit is a top tourist spot in Gunung Rinjani National Park. Despite being Indonesia\'s second highest peak, Rinjani remains active, with notable eruptions in 1884 and November 3, 1994, attracting adventurers, nature enthusiasts, researchers, and photographers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info42">
        A chain of islands appears to float in the Komodo Ocean. Initially arid, the islands transform with the clear, bluish sea water, blending brown and blue harmoniously. Komodo National Park, located in Manggarai, East Nusa Tenggara, comprises Komodo, Rinca, Padar, Gili Mota, Nusa Kode, and other small islands, serving as the habitat for the Komodo Dragon.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info43">
        Manupeu Tanah Daru National Park offers the charm of the Lapopu waterfall that amazes travelers on a journey full of challenges. Meanwhile, Laiwangi Wanggameti National Park in Sumba, which covers hilly areas to the horizon, has a dense canopy and plays an important role in storing water reserves that are much needed by local people during the dry season.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info45">
        At Kelimutu\'s peak in Ende, East Nusa Tenggara, three lakes bear witness to the ancestral spirits of the Lio community: red Atapolo for evil, Turquoise Nua Muri Koo Fai for youth, and Black Ata Mbupu for elders. Nearby, Perekonde rock marks the gateway where spirits are judged for their earthly deeds, according to the traditional beliefs of the Lio people.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info46">
        Standing elegantly at di Semenanjung Sanggar, Sumbawa Island, two decades ago, Tambora shaked the world. Nowadays, in its silence, Tambora offers a stunning beauty of nature and resources for humans around. Two years post-explosion, Tambora became a national park, spanning 71,645 hectares, designated by Indonesia\'s Ministry of Environment and Forestry.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info47">
        Aketajawe Lolobata National Park, spanning Central Halmahera, Kota Tidore Kepulauan, and East Halmahera, is renowned as a bird paradise. North Maluku has 243 bird species, with 26 being endemic; Halmahera hosts 211 bird species, 24 endemic. Endemic birds include the Invisible rail, Blue and white kingfisher, Halmahera cukcoo-shire, and Dusky-brown oriole.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info48">
        Manusela is a natural showcase for Seram\'s various ecosystems: beaches, swamp forests, lowland rain forests and mountain rain forests. From the coastline to the mountains, Manusela presents a variety of flora types on Seram Island. Starting from mangroves, beaches, swamp forests, river cliffs, tropical rain forests, mountain forests, to subalpine forests.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info49">
        The ocean defines Teluk Cendrawasih National Park\'s landscape, stretching endlessly. Nestled on the Pacific\'s edge, the park marks a significant tectonic meeting point. Over millennia, the geological history of this convergence has shaped the park\'s diverse ecosystems, resulting in rich biodiversity that encompasses both marine and terrestrial life forms.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info50">
        With 2.35 million hectares, this national park gained Asean Heritage Parks status in 2004. Renowned for its karst caves, Lorentz National Park boasts a complete ecosystem, from highlands to wetlands, attracting global recognition. It encompasses Mount Trikora and Jaya, with Cartenz summit boasting eternal snow, thus becoming a UNESCO World Heritage Site.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info51">
        Wasur\'s weather shifts with the seasons, marked by distinct patterns. The transition occurs during seasonal changes. In the rainy season, the swamp thrives, while it recedes during the dry season, leaving patches of water. Preservation reflects local wisdom, embodied in Merauke District\'s motto. Customary laws ensure harmony between humans and nature.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info52">
        Zamrud National Park in Siak, Riau, became the 52nd national park in 2016. Initially 30 hectares as the Wildlife Sanctuary of Lake Zamrud, it expanded to 31,340 hectares. Rich in peat swamp forest, it\'s home to 38 bird species, including protected ones like the White stork and hornbills. One iconic species is the Serindit Melayu (Lariculus galgulus).
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info53">
        In the same year as the declaration of Zamrud National Park, in the central part of Indonesia, precisely in the West Sulawesi Province, Gandang Dewata National Park was also born. This 53rd National Park is located in three regencies: Mamasa, Central Mamuju, and Mamuju. High biodiversity, authenticity, and uniqueness justify its national park designation.
    </string>
    <string name="taman_info54">
        Mount Maras, along with hills Nangka, Terang, Tambun Tulang, and Perayun, became the 54th national park in Indonesia on July 27, 2016. Located in Riau Silip and Kelapa sub-districts, Bangka Barat and Bangka, Bangka Belitung Province, Mount Maras National Park boasts a diverse ecosystem, merging mangrove, mountain, and lowland forests into one landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="ubah_bahasa">Change language</string>
    <string name="indonesia">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="inggris">English</string>
    <string name="tn1_a1">
        Exploring the natural beauty of Gunung Leuser National Park is a captivating adventure. Step by step, journey through the exquisite rainforest, teeming with rare plants and animals. Hear the birdsong, spot elusive Sumatran tigers, and witness orangutans swinging from tree to tree. This pristine wilderness offers a unique glimpse into nature\'s wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_a2">
        One of the best white water rafting spots in Indonesia is the Alas River. Commercial rafting was introduced here by SOBEK EXPEDITION in the 1970s. Rafting down the Alas River offers a unique view of Gunung Leuser National Park. From the rubber boat, adventurers can appreciate the natural beauty, diverse flora, and fauna while conquering the river rapids.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_a3">
        Rubbing, touching, and caressing the rough fur and thick skin of Sumatran elephants leaves a profound impression on tourists during the animal bathing experience. This close interaction allows visitors to connect deeply with these majestic creatures, creating lasting memories and a unique appreciation for wildlife conservation efforts in the region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_a4">
        Releasing hatchlings into the sea at Taman Nasional Gunung Leuseur, giving them a chance to grow and explore the underwater world\'s beauty, witnessing their transformation into majestic creatures, and being part of their incredible journey is a profound and unforgettable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_a5">
        Riding these gentle and majestic native elephants, who gracefully move through the lush forest, offers an unparalleled opportunity to immerse yourself in the awe-inspiring beauty of nature. Being enveloped by the serene surroundings of Gunung Leuser National Park, allows for a truly unforgettable and magical experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_kh1">
        The Sumatran Orangutan (Pongo abelii) has captivated tourists from around the world. Nestled in the picturesque Bukit Lawang Plantation Village, Bahorok, Langkat, the renowned Sumatran Orangutan Observation Center offers an amazing opportunity to observe these captivating creatures up close, making it a standout experience during adventure in Bukit Lawang.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_kh2">
        Embark on an adventurous journey by exploring the ecotourism area of Tangkahan in Batang Serangan, Langkat, North Sumatra, where you can experience riding magnificent Sumatran elephants. This hidden gem within Gunung Leuser National Park is renowned for its breathtaking landscapes and unique wildlife, making it a must-visit destination for nature lovers.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_kh3">
        As you embark on your journey through the breathtaking landscapes of Gunung Leuser, be prepared to immerse yourself in the rich and diverse ecosystem thriving within the boundaries of Gunung Leuser National Park. Your adventure will unveil the captivating presence of the endangered sea turtle, a majestic species that urgently requires our protection.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_kh4">
       The magnificent sight of Rafflesia atjehensis in Gunung Leuser National Park is truly a remarkable experience. This rare natural beauty captivates visitors with its large, striking flowers that can reach up to one meter in size. The sheer size and beauty of these flowers make them an unforgettable spectacle, showcasing the wonders of nature in their beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn1_kh5">
        Nestled within the rich, verdant surroundings of Gunung Leuser National Park lies the enchanting Pygmy Water Lily, a sight of a mystical beauty. As they gracefully bloom atop the water\'s surface, these delicate flowers imbue the landscape with an exquisite charm, add a touch of enchantment to the scenery, creating a truly picturesque sight worth beholding.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_a1">
        Embark on a thrilling adventure within the magnificent Batang Gadis National Park by immersing yourself in the exhilarating activity of tubing. Feel the rush as you navigate the river, surrounded by lush tropical greenery. Let the serenity of the forest and the adrenaline of the river combine to create unforgettable moments of pure joy and excitement.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_a2">
        Visit Batang Gadis National Park to discover the enchanting beauty of local culture presented in the traditional Sibanggor houses. These charming dwellings showcase well-preserved architecture, allowing you to step back in time and fully immerse yourself in the serene ambiance of this majestic wilderness, where nature\'s splendor unfolds at every turn.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_a3">
        Embark on an exciting hiking expedition through the lush trails of Batang Gadis National Park, where you can immerse yourself in the untouched beauty of nature. Feel the rush of adrenaline as you traverse through the breathtaking landscapes, with every step offering a new perspective and an opportunity to create lasting memories amidst the unspoiled wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_a4">
       Aek Cunek cascades gracefully down a sheer rock face, creating a mesmerizing spectacle as its crystal-clear waters plunge 100 meters below amidst lush greenery and vibrant floras. This breathtaking waterfall is a true natural wonder, offering visitors a serene escape into the heart of pristine wilderness and an opportunity to marvel at the beauty of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_kh1">
        The Sumatran Tiger, a magnificent creature imbued with both raw power and elegant poise, serves as a symbol of strength and grace within the vast wilderness of Batang Gadis National Park. Embark on a journey to this stunning location to behold firsthand the mesmerizing beauty and awe-inspiring presence of these majestic wild animals in their natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_kh2">
        Come and immerse yourself in the untamed beauty of Batang Gadis National Park where you can marvel at the magnificent Great Argus Pheasant, a true gem of the region. Witness firsthand the captivating wonder of wildlife as you behold this stunning bird in its natural habitat, surrounded by the breathtaking sights and sounds of nature\'s magnificence.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_kh3">
        Batang Gadis National Park is home to breathtaking natural beauty, with one of its most enchanting features being the exquisite Dancing Orchid. This flower captivates visitors with its elegance and beauty, making it a must-see destination for nature enthusiasts. Embark on a journey to explore this enchanting natural wonder in its mesmerizing splendor.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_kh4">
        Nepenthes, the carnivorous plant found in the lush and biodiverse Batang Gadis National Park, presents an extraordinary spectacle for those who venture into its depths. Surrounded by the magnificence beauty of the untamed wilderness, these insect-eating wonders add a touch fascination to the already mesmerizing landscape waiting to be discovered and admired.
    </string>
    <string name="tn2_kh5">
        In the lush environment of Batang Gadis National Park, the magnificent Rafflesia meijerri blooms harmoniously next to a myriad of enchanting wild mushrooms. As you traverse the park\'s trails, immerse yourself in the breathtaking spectacle of this unique beauty and be captivated by the endless marvels that nature unveils at every step of your journey.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_a1">
        Immerse yourself in the peaceful surroundings of Tesso Nilo National Park as you indulge in moments of pure relaxation while bird watching. Not only will you have the chance to observe fascinating wildlife, but you will also be treated to the sight of a diverse array of forest birds living harmoniously in their natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_a2">
        Embark on a remarkable journey of discovery through the elephant education program offered at Tesso Nilo National Park. This unique experience will provide a deep understanding of the daily life and the need for special protection of these majestic creatures. Get up close and personal with elephants, gaining insights that will stay with you forever.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_a3">
        Follow in the footsteps of environmental heroes in Tesso Nilo National Park by immersing yourself in the centuries-old martial art, Silat Pangean, which not only hones your physical skills but also connects you deeply with the rich cultural heritage of the region, providing a unique and enriching experience that combines tradition, nature, and growth.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_a4">
        Cherish the heartwarming sight of majestic elephants playfully reveling in the tranquility of their bathing ritual within the pristine landscapes of Tesso Nilo National Park. This encounter offers deep connection with these incredible creatures and allows you to immerse yourself in the wonders of the natural world, fostering a sense of awe and appreciation.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_a5">
        No need to worry about mud stains when exploring the forest, as the nature trail has been lined with durable paving blocks to ensure a clean and smooth journey. Visitors are not only shielded from muddy paths but also treated to a visually captivating experience, with majestic giant trees casting their cooling shadows along the three-kilometer trail.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_kh1">
        Tesso Nilo area has become one of the key conservation centers for wildlife habitats, with approximately 150 elephants. This vital sanctuary plays a crucial role in preserving biodiversity, offering a safe haven for these majestic creatures and other species. The conservation efforts help ensure the survival of endangered wildlife for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_kh2">
        The beauty of Tesso Nilo National Park is experienced through the enchantment of the wild, including the Rhinoceros Hornbill, which is an integral part of its ecosystem. The vibrant calls of the Hornbill echo through the trees, offering a glimpse into the intricate web of life that thrives here, creating a profound and immersive connection with nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_kh3">
        Explore the nocturnal life in Tesso Nilo National Park, where various types of frogs gather and create unique sounds. As the night unfolds, immerse yourself in the symphony of croaks and calls, discovering the vibrant ecosystem that comes alive after dark. The park\'s night-time ambiance, teeming with diverse wildlife, offers an unforgettable adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_kh4">
        Observing the colorful and cheerful variety of birds in Tesso Nilo National Park makes every adventure here unforgettable. The vibrant plumage and melodic songs of these birds create a captivating atmosphere, immersing you in the park\'s natural splendor. Each sighting and sound adds to the enchantment, leaving lasting impressions of the park\'s serene beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn3_kh5">
        The carnivorous pitcher plant, a unique insect-eating plant, is one of the fascinating species found in Tesso Nilo National Park. This plant has evolved to trap and digest insects, showcasing nature\'s ingenuity. Exploring the park, visitors can marvel at this extraordinary flora, making each visit a journey into the diverse world of tropical ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_a1">
       Enjoy the beauty of local culture with the traditional Turuk Laggai dance in Siberut National Park. This vibrant dance, rich in history and tradition, showcases the unique heritage of the indigenous people. Set against the backdrop of the lush landscapes, experiencing this dance offers a deep connection to the region\'s cultural roots and natural beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_a2">
        Immerse yourself in the unique cultural wisdom of the Siberut community, where age-old traditions and practices have been meticulously preserved for generations. Experience their harmonious way of living, deeply connected with nature, and gain insights into their rich heritage through their storytelling, rituals, and daily customs. A must-try experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_a3">
      Witness the beautiful moment of hatchling release, a symbol of new hope in the heart of the Siberut Forest. As the tiny creatures emerge from their shells, they embark on a journey filled with wonders. It is a moment that embodies the promise of a brighter future for the ecosystem and a touching reminder of the connection of all living beings.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_kh1">
       Captivated by the vibrant colors of the Asystasia Gangetica flowers that bloom in Siberut National Park, visitors often find themselves enchanted by the lush beauty of this remote paradise, where the delicate petals create a stunning contrast against the rich greenery, making it a truly unforgettable experience for nature enthusiasts and photographers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_kh2">
        Explore plant diversity by discovering the unique pitcher plant within the lush, vibrant Siberut forest, where this species thrives in its natural habitat. Experience the fascinating adaptations and ecological interactions that make the pitcher plant a captivating subject for botanists and nature enthusiasts alike, deepening our appreciation for the planet..
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_kh3">
        Nestled within the verdant expanse of Siberut National Park, the Montrouziera Cauliflora tree stands as a testament to nature\'s splendor. This rare botanical gem, with its majestic stature and unique cauliflory, captivates visitors with its unparalleled beauty, offering a glimpse into the extraordinary biodiversity of this pristine wilderness. Marvelous.
    </string>
    <string name="tn4_kh4">
       Let\'s embark on an expedition to uncover the mysteries of the Bilau Gibbon, a critically endangered primate species found exclusively in the lush rainforests of Siberut Island in Indonesia. These gibbons play a vital role in maintaining the ecological balance of their habitat, and studying them could provide invaluable insights of this unique ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_a1">
        Approaching the summit of Mount Kerinci, greenery becomes increasingly rare, giving way to a stark, rocky terrain that stretches toward the sky. At a glance, this crystal-clear panorama presents the tropical landscape of Sumatra, with its lush rainforests, winding rivers, and diverse wildlife, encapsulating the raw, untamed beauty of this Indonesian island.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_a2">
        Experience the breathtaking natural beauty of the Lumpo Waterfall in Kerinci Seblat National Park, where cascading waters create a mesmerizing sight. Nestled within the lush greenery of the park, this waterfall offers a serene escape into nature\'s embrace. Discover the tranquility of the surroundings as you immerse yourself in the sights of this hidden gem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_a3">
        Enjoy an exhilarating adventure as you navigate the meandering river in Kerinci Seblat National Park aboard a boat, immersing yourself in the enchanting natural beauty that surrounds you. Feel the thrill of discovery as you explore this pristine wilderness, home to a rich diversity of flora and fauna, creating beautiful memories that will last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_kh1">
        The Sumatran tiger, a majestic creature of unparalleled grace and power, gracefully roams the dense, emerald-green forests of Kerinci, its presence a testament to the untamed beauty of nature. Revered by locals, this regal feline is affectionately known as "Si Datuk," embodying the spirit of the jungle and captivating all who encounter its magnificence.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_kh2">
        Encounter the binturong, a unique animal in Kerinci Seblat National Park, a sprawling wilderness in Sumatra, Indonesia, where lush rainforests and diverse wildlife thrive. Known for its bear-like appearance and distinct scent reminiscent of popcorn, the binturong, the "bearcat," is a tree-dwelling mammal with a prehensile tail, making it an intriguing sight.
    </string>
    <string name="tn5_kh3">
        Shrouded in the dimness of the rainforest, the Rafflesia arnoldi flower blooms in a burst of color, as if painting the wilderness with its vivid hues, a botanical marvel that captivates with its enormity and intricate details, inviting admiration from those fortunate enough to witness nature\'s grandeur displayed in this spectacle of floral magnificence.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_a1">
        Enjoy an exciting adventure with hiking in Bukit Duabelas National Park, where lush rainforest, diverse wildlife, and rich indigenous cultures converge to create a truly unforgettable experience. Trek through pristine landscapes, encounter rare flora and fauna, and immerse yourself in the traditions of local communities, making memories that last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_a2">
        Embrace the hospitality of the Orang Rimba community by visiting their traditional houses in Bukit Duabelas National Park, nestled in the heart of Sumatra\'s lush landscapes. Engage in their unique way of life, learn their ancestral traditions, and savor the simplicity and harmony of their culture, creating unforgettable memories that will last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_a3">
        Meet the Orang Rimba community, an indigenous group living in harmony with nature within the lush confines of Bukit Duabelas National Park. Their way of life is a testament to the rich tapestry of cultural diversity found in Indonesia, showcasing traditions, beliefs, and practices that have endured for generations. Nature and humanity are truly intertwined.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_kh1">
        Siamang, one of the many amazing creatures you\'ll encounter in Bukit Duabelas National Park, swings gracefully through the verdant canopy, its melodic calls echoing through the lush foliage. This captivating biodiversity hotspot teems with life, offering a mesmerizing tapestry of flora and fauna, each species intricately woven into the web of the ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_kh2">
        Bulbophyllum Patens, one of the many plants thriving in Bukit Duabelas National Park, stands as a testament to the intricate beauty of nature, showcasing its vibrant hues amidst the lush greenery. A natural wonder deserving of preservation, it serves as a reminder of the delicate balance we must maintain to safeguard the biodiversity of our planet.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_kh3">
        Dipodium Scardens, an exotic orchid thriving in Bukit Duabelas National Park, adds a touch of rare beauty to the already enchanting natural landscape. With its delicate petals and vibrant colors, this orchid stands out as a symbol of the park\'s rich biodiversity, inviting visitors to marvel at its unique allure and appreciate the wonders of the world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_kh4">
        Meranti Bunga, a remarkable plant that is a vital part of Bukit Duabelas National Park\'s ecosystem, stands as a natural wonder that must be conserved. Its presence not only enriches the biodiversity of the park but also serves as a testament to the delicate balance of nature that must be preserved for future generations to marvel at and appreciate.
    </string>
    <string name="tn6_kh5">
        Nepenthes, the carnivorous plant found in the lush expanses of Bukit Duabelas National Park, stands as a testament to the rich biodiversity of our natural world—a treasure trove of life forms and ecological wonders that we must strive to protect and preserve, a responsibility that falls on all of us, to ensure a sustainable future for generations to come.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_a1">
        Come to experience an extraordinary adventure with Jungle Run in Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, where you can immerse yourself in the thrill of the wild while surrounded by breathtaking natural beauty. Feel the adrenaline rush as you navigate through rugged terrain and dense jungle, encountering exotic wildlife and stunning landscapes along the way.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_a2">
        Speed across the water on a speedboat in Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, reveling in the rush of adrenaline as you glide along the mesmerizing river at high speed, surrounded by the lush greenery of the rainforest, the symphony of wildlife echoing in the air, creating an unforgettable adventure that ignites the spirit of exploration and wonder within you.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_a3">
        In Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, an expanse of natural beauty, camping offers a glimpse into the wilderness, while trailing unveils hidden treasures of the jungle. Hiking through its lush trails promises adventure and serenity intertwined, while bird watching invites enthusiasts to marvel at the diverse avian species thriving in this haven of exploration.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_kh1">
        The Crimson-winged Woodpecker, one of the many birds that enhance the biodiversity of Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, dazzles with its vibrant plumage, adding a mesmerizing splash of natural color to the park\'s tapestry. Amidst the lush greenery, its crimson wings stand out, a testament to the exquisite beauty found within the diverse ecosystem of wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_kh2">
        The Hornbill, a giant bird with a striking beak that plays an essential role in the ecosystem of Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, represents a natural uniqueness that needs to be preserved, serving as a symbol of the balance and rich biodiversity of this extraordinary habitat, showcasing nature\'s evolutionary marvels and the connection of all living beings.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_kh3">
        The Tapir, an exotic herbivorous animal that roams the forests of Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, is a unique and fascinating creature. It plays a crucial role in maintaining the ecosystem. A natural wonder that must be conserved, the Tapir\'s presence highlights the importance of preserving biodiversity and protecting these creatures for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_kh4">
       The Copper-cheeked Frog, a water-dwelling creature essential for the biodiversity of Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, plays a crucial role in maintaining the ecological balance. This amphibian not only contributes to the health of aquatic ecosystems but also serves as an indicator of environmental changes, reflecting the overall health of the park\'s habitats.
    </string>
    <string name="tn7_kh5">
        The Sumatran Tiger, a captivating predator in Bukit Tigapuluh National Park, serves as a symbol of the beauty and power of nature. This majestic creature roams the dense forests and is crucial for maintaining the ecological balance, highlighting the urgent need for conservation efforts to protect its dwindling population and preserve its natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_a1">
        Come and enjoy the beauty of nature while bird-watching in Berbak and Sembilang National Park, where lush mangroves and tropical rainforests provide a haven for diverse bird species. Witness vibrant plumage, unique behaviors, and the tranquil sounds of birdsong as you explore one of Indonesia\'s most stunning and ecologically significant natural reserves.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_a2">
        Explore the beauty of the rivers by boat in Berbak and Sembilang National Park. This exciting water adventure allows you to immerse yourself in stunning natural landscapes, observe diverse wildlife, and experience the beauty of untouched forests. Whether you\'re a nature enthusiast or seeking a peaceful escape, this journey promises unforgettable memories.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_a3">
        Immerse yourself in nature through trailing in Berbak and Sembilang National Park. Embark on a winding adventure through the breathtaking forest, where the lush greenery, diverse wildlife, and serene landscapes create an unforgettable experience. Discover the hidden gems of this pristine wilderness, and let the tranquility of nature rejuvenate your spirit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_a4">
        Witness the beauty of the sunrise from Dusun Sembilang in Berbak and Sembilang National Park, where the sky transforms into a canvas of vibrant hues, painting a wonderful masterpiece. As the sun ascends, its golden rays illuminate the landscape, awakening the flora and fauna in a symphony of nature\'s glory—a truly inspiring morning that rejuvenates the soul.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_a5">
        Learn about the traditional process of making shrimp paste in Berbak and Sembilang National Park, where generations have passed down the meticulous craft, transforming fresh catches into a rich, savory condiment. This cultural lesson is a sensory experience, filled with the pungent aroma, showcasing the deep-rooted traditions of the local community.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_kh1">
       The Sumatran Elephant, one of the dominant animals in the biodiversity of Berbak and Sembilang National Park, stands as a majestic symbol of the region\'s natural wonders, its presence echoing the delicate balance of its ecosystem and underscoring the need for preservation efforts to safeguard this magnificent creature and its habitat for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_kh2">
        Crocodiles, powerful predators living in the rivers of Berbak and Sembilang National Park, are an integral part of the river ecosystem, playing crucial roles in maintaining ecological balance by regulating prey populations and contributing to nutrient cycling, thus underscoring the significance of conserving their habitat for the region\'s biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_kh3">
        Cockatoos, exotic birds that adorn the skies of Berbak and Sembilang National Park, add to the captivating fauna diversity found in this remarkable region, where lush mangrove forests meet expansive wetlands, creating a haven for an array of unique wildlife species, making it a must-visit destination for nature enthusiasts and conservationists alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_kh4">
        Orangutans, charming primates that live in the forests of Berbak and Sembilang National Park, are an inspiring example of biodiversity, embodying the rich tapestry of life found in these pristine habitats. Their presence highlights the delicate balance of ecosystems and the importance of conservation efforts to protect these creatures and their environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn8_kh5">
        The Pitcher Plant, a unique carnivorous plant native to Berbak and Sembilang National Park in Indonesia, thrives in the park\'s wetlands, showcasing the area\'s rich biodiversity. This unique flora not only adds to the park\'s ecological importance but also serves as a symbol of the need for preservation efforts to protect such rare and valuable species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_a1">
        Dare to try white water rafting in Cilik River? Feel the thrilling adventure in Bukit Barisan Selatan National Park as you navigate the river\'s twists and turns, surrounded by lush tropical rainforest teeming with exotic wildlife. It\'s a thrilling experience that will leave you with unforgettable memories of your journey through stunning natural landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_a2">
        Nestled within the verdant expanse of the Bukit Barisan Selatan National Park, the Talang Bukit crater captivates with its breathtaking beauty, offering a glimpse into the raw, natural splendor of Indonesia. The crater, a testament to the earth\'s fiery past, stands as a reminder of nature\'s enduring power and the captivating allure of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_a3">
        Come to gain insights into the environment at Bukit Barisan Selatan National Park by participating in the phenology learning program at Way Canguk Research Station, where you can observe the park\'s rich biodiversity, learn about its unique ecosystems, and contribute to ongoing conservation efforts through hands-on fieldwork led by experienced researchers.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_kh1">
        The biodiversity of Bukit Barisan Selatan National Park also includes exotic turtles, adding to its allure as a sanctuary for unique flora and fauna. Turtles, ranging from the critically endangered pig-nosed turtle to the majestic leatherback, find refuge in the park\'s lush habitats, contributing to its status as a globally significant conservation area.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_kh2">
        The great hornbill, a majestic bird known for its impressive size and vibrant plumage, chooses to construct its nests in the secluded embrace of tree cavities deep within the verdant expanse of the forest, where it finds solace and security for its precious offspring amidst the whispering leaves and dappled sunlight filtering through the canopy above.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_kh3">
        Rafflesia arnoldii, renowned as the world\'s largest flower, thrives in the rainforests of Southeast Asia, particularly on the liana tree trunks of the Sumatran rainforest, where its massive, red, and white petals unfurl, emitting a putrid odor to attract insects for pollination, making it a fascinating rare sight for botanists and nature enthusiasts alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn10_kh4">
        The Sumatran elephant, one of the key species in the biodiversity of Bukit Barisan Selatan National Park, stands as a majestic symbol of nature\'s intricacy. Its presence not only enriches the ecosystem but also serves as a poignant reminder of our responsibility to safeguard these irreplaceable treasures for future generations to marvel at and cherish.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_a1">
        Come and enjoy a camping adventure in Way Kambas National Park, where you can immerse yourself in the untouched beauty of nature. As night falls, the sky transforms into a mesmerizing display of stars, offering a breathtaking view that truly connects you with the wilderness, creating an unforgettable experience that beckons to be revisited time and again.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_a2">
        Join exciting tours in Way Kambas National Park and immerse yourself in the natural riches and local culture. Discover the park\'s diverse wildlife, including elephants and tigers, as experienced guides lead you through lush jungles and serene rivers. Experience traditional dances and taste local cuisine, creating unforgettable memories of this destination.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_a3">
        Experience a special moment of feeding elephants in Way Kambas National Park, where you\'ll connect with the gentle giants, offering them food and feeling the brush of their trunks as they gracefully take it from your hand. This interaction provides a rare glimpse into the lives of these majestic creatures, leaving a lasting impact on your heart and mind.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_a4">
        Come and observe the beauty of wild birds in Way Kambas National Park, where an amazing bird-watching experience awaits. Marvel at the vibrant plumage and melodious songs of countless avian species as you immerse yourself in the lush surroundings of this biodiverse sanctuary, a haven for both seasoned ornithologists and curious nature enthusiasts alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_a5">
        Witness the cultural beauty with Lampung dance in Way Kambas National Park, where the rhythmic movements of traditional dance forms illuminate the lush wilderness, offering a mesmerizing fusion of nature and culture. Here, amidst the verdant splendor, ancient traditions thrive, echoing the vibrant heartbeat of a rich heritage rooted in the natural landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_kh1">
        The Sumatran rhinoceros, one of the protected species in Way Kambas National Park, symbolizes the rich biodiversity that needs to be preserved for future generations. These majestic creatures, with their distinctive features and critical role in the ecosystem, serve as a reminder of our responsibility to safeguard the delicate balance of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_kh2">
        Bears, powerful animals living in the forests of Way Kambas National Park, roam the lush wilderness, their presence adding to the extraordinary natural wealth of the region. With their majestic stature and untamed beauty, these creatures embody the essence of the park\'s unspoiled wilderness, captivating all who encounter them with their grace and power.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_kh3">
        Tigers, powerful predators and one of the icons of Way Kambas National Park, roam its lush forests, their majestic presence a source of pride for nature enthusiasts and conservationists alike. The park\'s diverse ecosystems, home to these magnificent creatures, highlight the importance of preserving this habitat and the rich biodiversity it supports.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_kh4">
        Elephants, creatures that roam the forests of Way Kambas National Park, captivate with their grandeur, their gentle yet powerful presence an inseparable part of biodiversity. They embody resilience, their lumbering grace a testament to the intricate balance of nature, fostering awe and reverence among those fortunate enough to witness their majestic  strides.
    </string>
    <string name="tn11_kh5">
        Rimba Duck, a rare bird that is a hallmark of Way Kambas National Park, epitomizes the captivating charm of wildlife, drawing visitors into a realm where nature\'s wonders unfold. Its vibrant plumage and graceful movements mesmerize onlookers, offering a glimpse into the delicate balance of ecosystems, a profound respect for the natural world\'s intricacies.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_a1">
        Enjoy a peaceful night at the camping ground in Gunung Palung National Park, where the fresh natural ambiance and shining stars create a serene and magical atmosphere. Surrounded by lush rainforest and the sounds of nocturnal wildlife, you\'ll find yourself immersed in nature\'s tranquility, making it an unforgettable experience under the vast, starlit sky.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_a2">
        Experience tubing adventure in the rivers of Gunung Palung National Park, where the thrill of navigating challenging water currents awaits. Feel the rush of adrenaline as you maneuver through twists and turns, surrounded by the lush beauty of the rainforest. This exhilarating journey promises unforgettable memories and a unique way to connect with nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_a3">
        Explore the natural beauty around Lubuk Baji waterfall in Gunung Palung National Park. The lush greenery, cascading waters, and serene atmosphere create a breathtaking and tranquil environment. Whether hiking through the forest trails or simply relaxing by the falls, this stunning view is one to be savored and remembered for its untouched splendor.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_a4">
        Witness the beauty of Riam Berasap waterfall in Gunung Palung National Park. This stunning natural wonder is a perfect spot to relax, unwind, and immerse yourself in the serene ambiance of the lush rainforest. Enjoy the soothing sounds of cascading water and the vibrant flora and fauna that surround this stunning waterfall. Truly an unforgettable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_a5">
        Enjoy the breathtaking view at Riam Bekinjil in Gunung Palung National Park, where lush greenery and cascading waterfalls create an unforgettable natural wonder. Whether you\'re an avid hiker or simply seeking tranquility, this pristine location offers a perfect escape. Immerse yourself in nature\'s beauty and let the serene ambiance rejuvenate your spirit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_kh1">
        Acanthomenexenus Polyacanthus, one of the various rare species in Gunung Palung National Park, stands out for its distinctive characteristics. Its unique presence is a natural attraction, drawing scientists, researchers, and nature enthusiasts from around the world who are eager to observe and study this remarkable species in its pristine, natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_kh2">
        Red-Naped Trogon, a beautiful bird with striking red hues on its body, is one of the many inhabitants of Gunung Palung National Park. This enchanting species adds to the park\'s incredible biodiversity, captivating visitors with its vivid plumage and melodic calls. The bird\'s presence highlights the park\'s role in preserving the regions rich natural beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn12_kh3">
        Orangutans, highly endangered great apes, also call Gunung Palung National Park home. Their presence is a valuable legacy of nature, symbolizing the rich biodiversity and ecological importance of this unique habitat. Conservation efforts in the park are crucial for ensuring the survival of these majestic creatures and preserving the future natural heritage.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_a1">
        Feel the thrill of water adventure with kayaking in Bentarum National Park, an activity suitable for all ages that promises unforgettable moments amidst stunning natural landscapes. Glide through serene waters, surrounded by lush greenery, as you embark on an exhilarating journey, creating cherished memories with friends and family that will last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_a2">
        Experience the tranquil allure of nature as you leisurely drift along the meandering rivers of Bentarum National Park, soaking in the serenity and joy of tubing. An ideal getaway beckons for families and friends, promising cherished moments amidst picturesque landscapes and shared laughter, creating unforgettable memories to treasure for a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_a3">
        Come and enjoy spectacular views with a cruise tour in Bentarum National Park, where verdant landscapes meet azure waters, creating an unforgettable sailing experience. Glide along serene coastlines, witness majestic cliffs, and marvel at diverse wildlife as you embark on this adventure of a lifetime, immersing yourself in the beauty of nature\'s grandeur.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_kh1">
        Orangutans, highly endangered great apes, also call Bentarum National Park home. Their presence is a valuable legacy of nature, a testament to the delicate balance of ecosystems and the importance of preserving biodiversity for future generations to marvel at and learn from, highlighting the connections of all living beings in the intricate web of life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_kh2">
       Marvel at the beauty of the Super Red Arowana that shines in Bentarum National Park, captivating onlookers with its radiant hues amidst the serene waters. The enchanting underwater world\'s charm beckons adventurers to explore its depths, where vibrant corals dance and elusive creatures hide, creating a mesmerizing spectacle that leaves a lasting impression.
    </string>
    <string name="tn13_kh3">
        Explore Bentarum National Park and immerse yourself in the mesmerizing world of its diverse wildlife. From the graceful movements of the Huntsman Spider to the colorful plumage of tropical birds, every corner of the park offers a glimpse into nature\'s captivating beauty and rich biodiversity, making it an unforgettable experience for nature enthusiasts.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_a1">
        Create unforgettable memories at the camping ground in Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park where you can immerse yourself in the beauty of nature, surrounded by lush greenery and towering trees. Revel in the serenity of starry nights, as you bond with loved ones around a crackling campfire, making every moment a cherished memory to last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_a2">
       Challenge yourself with the ascent of Bukit Raya in Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park. The climb can be demanding, but the summit offers extraordinary views that make your efforts worthwhile. Along the way, you\'ll encounter diverse wildlife, lush rainforests, and the serene beauty of nature, ensuring a truly rewarding adventure for any avid hiker.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_a3">
        Experience the wonders of nature while observing wildlife in Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park. See the diverse creatures living freely in their habitat, from colorful birds and playful primates to elusive big cats. Immerse yourself in the lush rainforest, where every step reveals a new marvel, and feel the tranquility that only such beauty can provide.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_a4">
        Explore the beauty of the waters by boat in Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park. Enjoy the tranquility of the water and the surrounding nature, taking in the lush greenery, diverse wildlife, and serene atmosphere. Let the gentle flow of the river guide you through a breathtaking landscape, providing a perfect escape from the hustle and bustle of daily life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_a5">
        Feel the adrenaline rush as you navigate the rapids of the Ella Hulu River, nestled within the pristine beauty of Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park. This thrilling adventure offers an unforgettable journey through untamed wilderness, where every twist and turn brings a new thrill, immersing you in the raw power and majesty of nature\'s untamed spirit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_kh1">
        Sneaking into the Bukit Baka – Bukit Raya forest, we are greeted by the lively sounds of wild animals, among which the gentle chattering of the Slow Loris resonates. The playful sounds of this nocturnal creature intertwine with the rustle of leaves and the distant calls of birds, crafting a soothing symphony that envelops us in the nature\'s serenity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_kh2">
        Witness the enchanting Rajah Brooke\'s Birdwing butterflies gracefully fluttering amidst the lush greenery of the tropical forest, their vibrant hues painting a mesmerizing tableau against the backdrop of emerald foliage, a breathtaking spectacle that epitomizes the harmony of nature\'s intricate beauty and the delicate dance of life in its purest form.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_kh3">
        Sambar Deer, the magnificent animals, gracefully roam within the lush expanse of Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park, their elegant strides painting a picture of serene wilderness. Amidst towering trees and babbling streams, they embody the harmonious balance of nature, adding to the park\'s allure as a haven for biodiversity and a sanctuary for enthusiasts.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_kh4">
        Discover the awe-inspiring spectacle of the Amorphophallus Hewittii plant as it bursts into bloom amidst the breathtaking landscapes of Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park. Immerse yourself in the unparalleled richness of nature\'s tapestry, where a myriad of plant species coexist in harmonious abundance, awaiting your exploration and deep admiration.
    </string>
    <string name="tn14_kh5">
        Rhododendron Mageanum, an exotic flowering plant, thrives in Bukit Baka Bukit Raya National Park, its vibrant blooms a testament to the richness of biodiversity. The endless beauty of nature in every corner enchants visitors, offering a sanctuary where tranquility intertwines with the vibrant hues of blossoms, creating a symphony of color and life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_a1">
        The parked klotok boats, with their vibrant colors and sturdy frames, line the banks, eagerly awaiting to ferry visitors along the meandering bends and lush banks of the Sekonyer River, offering an immersive journey through the heart of Borneo\'s rich biodiversity and captivating landscapes, creating unforgettable memories for all who embark upon their decks.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_a2">
        Tracking, an exciting experience of traversing the open wilderness in Tanjung Puting National Park, immerses adventurers in a realm where lush canopies embrace curious eyes, echoing with the symphony of wildlife. Each step unveils secrets of ancient forests, fostering a profound connection between explorers and the untamed beauty of nature\'s sanctuaries.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_a3">
       Foreign tourists, equipped with cameras and binoculars, are highly engaged in documenting the majestic Orangutans residing at Camp Leakey, their lenses capturing every nuanced movement and expression of these remarkable primates, as they traverse the lush greenery of the rainforest, weaving tales of conservation and admiration for these endangered mammals.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_kh1">
        Orangutans, the icons of wildlife in Tanjung Puting National Park, swing gracefully through the lush canopies of Borneo\'s rainforests, their auburn fur blending seamlessly with the verdant foliage as they forage for ripe fruits, their gentle demeanor captivating the hearts of visitors and researchers alike, symbolizing the fine balance of nature\'s wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_kh2">
        In the verdant canopy, a troupe of Proboscis Monkeys, with their distinctive long noses, gather under the leadership of the dominant male. Their silhouettes against the lush foliage create a mesmerizing sight, as they navigate the dense foliage with agile grace, their unique facial feature distinguishing the leader amidst the verdant expanse of the treetops.
    </string>
    <string name="tn16_kh3">
        The variety of life in Tanjung Puting National Park encompasses an extraordinary array of biodiversity, including the majestic Nephila Pilipes Spiders, renowned for their intricate webs and impressive size, weaving their presence into the intricate tapestry of this rich ecosystem, captivating visitors with their remarkable beauty and ecological significance.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_a1">
        Nestled within the lush expanse of Sebangau National Park, a sanctuary of verdant foliage and pristine waterways, lies a spectacle of nature\'s finest avian residents. Here, amidst the tranquil melodies of rustling leaves and flowing streams, one can marvel at the vibrant plumage and graceful flight of the diverse bird species that call this sanctuary home.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_a2">
        Embarking on an unforgettable adventure, trekking in the untouched wilderness of Sebangau, immersed ourselves in nature\'s raw beauty, traversing dense forests, encountering exotic wildlife, and forging bonds under the vast canopy of the jungle, creating memories that would forever resonate with the echoes of distant rivers and the whispers of trees.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_a3">
        Navigate the winding river and immerse yourself in the rich biodiversity of Sebangau, where lush rainforests teem with unique wildlife, including endangered orangutans, exotic birds, and diverse aquatic life. Experience the serene beauty and ecological wonders of this pristine environment, making it a paradise for nature lovers and adventurers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_kh1">
        The vibrant life in Sebangau National Park is a tapestry of wonders, where the ethereal beauty of Golden Pheasants adorns the sky, their majestic plumage a kaleidoscope of hues dancing amidst the verdant canopy, echoing nature\'s symphony, inviting all who wander into its embrace to behold its timeless splendor and cherish its precious biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_kh2">
        Life in Sebangau National Park unfolds amid the lush greenery, where the captivating Nepenthes Pitcher Plants sway in the gentle breeze, their carnivorous allure captivating curious eyes. Yet beneath this facade lies a realm of hidden predators, each adapting to survive in this intricate ecosystem, where every encounter is a delicate dance of life and death.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_kh3">
        Orangutans Pongo pygmaeus, guardians of the forest and natural wonders in Sebangau, swing gracefully through the lush canopy, their reddish-brown coats blending seamlessly with the verdant foliage as they navigate their treetop realm with unparalleled agility, offering a captivating glimpse into the harmonious coexistence of wildlife and pristine wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_kh4">
        Biodiversity in Sebangau National Park: the Crimson-headed Trogon bird, with its vibrant plumage and distinctive call echoing through the dense canopy, shares its habitat with an array of equally captivating species, contributing to the park\'s rich ecological tapestry and serving as a testament to the intricate connections of nature\'s wonders.
        forest.
    </string>
    <string name="tn17_kh5">
        The enchanting beauty of nature in Sebangau National Park is epitomized by the mesmerizing presence of Bulbophyllum reticulatum Orchids, their delicate petals painting vibrant strokes against the lush backdrop of verdant foliage, where each bloom tells a story of resilience and harmony, encapsulating the essence of biodiversity in its most captivating form.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_a1">
       Witness captivating local dances in Kayan Mentarang National Park, where the rhythmic movements of traditional performers intertwine with the lush surroundings, epitomizing the living beauty of culture. Immerse yourself in the vibrant energy as dancers gracefully express centuries-old traditions, connecting visitors to the rich heritage of the land.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_a2">
        Explore the cultural richness enveloping Kayan Mentarang National Park, an enchanting sanctuary where biodiversity thrives in harmony with indigenous traditions. Engage with the warm embrace of local communities, eager to share their vibrant heritage and age-old customs, offering a profound journey into the heart of cultural diversity and natural wonder.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_a3">
        Experience the enchanting rhythms of life within the captivating expanse of Kayan Mentarang National Park, where the vibrant tapestry of local culture unfolds against a backdrop of breathtaking natural splendor. Immerse yourself in the intricacies of daily existence, savoring the harmonious blend of tradition and the untouched beauty of the wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_a4">
        Observe the salt processing in Kayan Mentarang National Park, where the rhythmic motions of workers intertwine with the natural landscape, revealing the intricate dance of human endeavor amidst untouched wilderness. It\'s a poignant reminder of the delicate balance between civilization and nature, where each grain of salt tells a story of meaningful daily life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_kh1">
        Agile Gibbons, exotic primates in Kayan Mentarang National Park, add to the charm of biodiversity, their melodic calls echoing through the dense foliage, weaving into the symphony of nature. Their presence is a special part of the wilderness, captivating visitors with their acrobatic displays and enriching the ecosystem with their vital role as seed dispersers.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_kh2">
        Eagles, majestic predators, make Kayan Mentarang National Park their home, soaring through its expansive skies with an unparalleled sense of freedom. The allure of their graceful flight captivates visitors, offering a glimpse into the untamed beauty of nature and the symbiotic relationship between these magnificent birds and their pristine habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_kh3">
        Pythons, the amazing giant snakes, are one of the fascinating inhabitants of Kayan Mentarang National Park, where the lush rainforest echoes with their silent slithering. Their presence adds to the mysterious wonder of nature, captivating visitors with their majestic coils and enigmatic gaze, inviting exploration into the depths of this biodiverse sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_kh4">
        Neptis columella, an exotic butterfly native to the lush environs of Kayan Mentarang National Park, gracefully adorns the forest with its vibrant and intricately patterned wings, adding a captivating dimension to the park\'s rich biodiversity, a testament to nature\'s artistry and the delicate balance of ecosystems thriving within this verdant sanctuary of life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn18_kh5">
        Rafflesia, the rare giant flower, thrives in Kayan Mentarang National Park, where its breathtaking presence adds to the unforgettable natural beauty of the landscape, drawing visitors from around the globe who are captivated by its stunning petals and intrigued by the intricate ecosystem it inhabits, making every moment spent there a cherished memory.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_a1">
        Canoe in Kutai National Park and explore the amazing river, navigating through lush greenery and diverse wildlife. Engage in an exciting water adventure in the heart of the wilderness, where every paddle stroke unveils a new spectacle of nature\'s beauty, promising unforgettable moments and thrilling experiences for adventurers seeking untamed landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_a2">
        Enjoy beautiful views in Kutai National Park. Captivating natural beauty ready to be explored awaits you at every turn. Traverse lush forests teeming with life, discover cascading waterfalls hidden within verdant valleys, and encounter rare wildlife thriving in their natural habitat. Experience the wonder of nature like never before in this majestic sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_a3">
        Explore the fascinating depths of Gua Sampekmarta, nestled within the enchanting realm of Kutai National Park, where an awe-inspiring adventure unfolds amidst the darkness, revealing hidden wonders awaiting discovery. Embark on a journey into the subterranean realm, where mystery and marvel intertwine, promising an unforgettable experience beyond imagination.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_a4">
        Experience the vibrant rhythm and melodies of live music amidst the lush beauty of Kutai National Park, creating an electrifying ambiance that resonates with every beat. It\'s a lively atmosphere, inviting you to revel in the shared joy and immerse yourself in the harmonious fusion of nature and music, an unforgettable experience for all to cherish.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_a5">
        Paddle with a kayak in Kutai National Park and savor the beauty of a water adventure, immersing yourself in the tranquil surroundings while navigating pristine waters, an experience that rejuvenates both body and soul, offering a refreshing activity in the great outdoors, perfect for nature enthusiasts seeking moments of serenity amidst majestic landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_kh1">
        Dracontomelum dao, an exotic tree with lush foliage and vibrant blossoms, gracefully adorns the verdant landscape of Kutai National Park. Its presence not only enhances the park\'s aesthetic appeal but also contributes to the intricate web of life, fostering biodiversity and sustaining a balance within this captivating ecosystem of unparalleled natural beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_kh2">
        In Kutai National Park, monitor lizards gracefully roam, their sleek bodies blending with the lush surroundings. Their existence within this ecological enriches the tapestry of diverse wildlife. With their keen senses and distinctive appearance, they captivate the attention of all who venture into this pristine wilderness, embodying the park\'s biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_kh3">
        Myriapods, diverse insects, are an integral part of Kutai National Park\'s natural environment, contributing to its intricate web of life. They embody the limitless uniqueness of the insect world, showcasing nature\'s boundless creativity and adaptation. From tiny millipedes to industrious ants, each species plays a vital role in sustaining the park\'s ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_kh4">
        Lanternflies, enchanting insects, adorn Kutai National Park with their vibrant colors, their delicate wings weaving through the lush foliage. Captivating biodiversity thrives in this sanctuary, a symphony of life\'s myriad forms. From the majestic canopy to the forest floor, every corner teems with nature\'s enchantment, a testament to the park\'s pristine allure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn19_kh5">
        Liverworts are one of the fascinating elements of Kutai National Park. These small, non-vascular plants contribute significantly to the biodiversity of the region. The intriguing plant life in the magnificent forest environment showcases the park\'s rich natural heritage and plays a crucial role in maintaining the ecological balance and supporting wildlife.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_a1">
        Explore the natural beauty of Bantimurung Bulusaraung National Park with challenging tracking activities, where lush rainforests teem with diverse flora and fauna, offering a glimpse into the rich biodiversity of the region. Immerse yourself in the sights and sounds of this pristine wilderness, discovering hidden waterfalls and encountering rare species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_a2">
        Enjoy spectacular views from the Helena Sky Bridge, a perfect spot to see this national park\'s panorama. The bridge stretches gracefully across the valley, offering a breathtaking vantage point for capturing the majestic beauty of the landscape below. Whether you\'re a nature enthusiast or a casual observer, this experience promises to be unforgettable.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_a3">
        Elevate your adventure with hiking amidst the stunning biodiversity of Bantimurung Bulusaraung, where forests teem with exotic flora and fauna, cascading waterfalls offer a symphony of nature\'s melody, and rugged trails unveil panoramic vistas that stir the soul, beckoning explorers to immerse themselves in the untamed beauty of this wilderness sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_a4">
        Witness the beauty of butterflies in the activity of butterfly watching in Bantimurung Bulusaraung National Park, where vibrant wings dance amidst lush greenery, a testament to nature\'s artistry. Immerse yourself in the kaleidoscope of colors as these delicate creatures flutter gracefully, offering a glimpse into the complex and enchanting world of butterflies.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_a5">
        Witness the beauty of butterflies in the activity of butterfly watching in Bantimurung Bulusaraung National Park, where vibrant wings dance amidst lush greenery, a testament to nature\'s artistry. Immerse yourself in the kaleidoscope of colors as these delicate creatures flutter gracefully, offering a glimpse into the complex and enchanting world of butterflies.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_kh1">
        Witness the splendor of the rare Sulawesi hornbills, with their striking plumage and majestic flight, when visiting Bantimurung Bulusaraung National Park. This protected area, nestled in the heart of Indonesia, is renowned for its breathtaking biodiversity, offering a glimpse into the rich tapestry of life that thrives in this pristine natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_kh2">
        Be mesmerized by the variety of colors of Graphium Androcles butterflies that adorn this national park, where their delicate wings flutter amidst the lush greenery, creating a picturesque scene that captivates visitors and photographers alike, showcasing nature\'s intricate beauty in every hue and pattern, a testament to the park\'s rich biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_kh3">
        Watch the playful macaca Maura troop in the tropical forests of Bantimurung Bulusaraung National Park, as they swing effortlessly from branch to branch, their vibrant coats shimmering in the dappled sunlight filtering through the dense canopy, echoing with their melodic calls and creating a mesmerizing symphony of nature\'s beauty and its biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn20_kh4">
        Meet the Tarsius Fuscus, a small primate that can only be found in the forests of Sulawesi, in this national park, where it thrives amidst lush greenery and diverse wildlife, showcasing its unique behavior and intricate social structures, providing researchers and nature enthusiasts alike with a fascinating glimpse into the complexities of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_a1">
        Emotional moment when baby turtles, after hatching under the protective cover of night, are gently released into the open sea of Taka Bonerate National Park by conservationists, their tiny forms navigating the vastness, guided by an ancient instinct, beginning a perilous journey filled with unknown challenges, yet kindled with hope for a future generation.
        adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_a2">
        Enjoy the sensation of swimming in the clear and warm waters of Taka Bonerate National Park, where the azure sky meets the sparkling sea, creating a breathtaking backdrop for an unforgettable aquatic experience, surrounded by the vibrant marine life and stunning coral reefs that make this destination a paradise for nature lovers and adventure seekers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_a3">
        Explore the mesmerizing beauty of the underwater world by snorkeling in the stunning coral reefs, where a kaleidoscope of marine life dances amidst vibrant hues, offering an immersive experience into nature\'s masterpiece, a realm where tranquility meets wonder, leaving an indelible mark on the soul, igniting a passion for conservation and exploration.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_kh1">
        Encounter the powerful blacktip sharks in the crystal-clear waters of Taka Bonerate National Park, a UNESCO Biosphere Reserve and Indonesia\'s largest atoll. Dive into the midst of these sleek predators, witnessing their graceful movements and observing their natural behavior in their pristine marine habitat, an experience that will stay with you forever.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_kh2">
        Witness the majestic and rare green sea turtles in these waters of Taka Bonerate National Park, where these ancient mariners gracefully glide through crystal-clear waters, their ancient, prehistoric forms a testament to the enduring beauty and resilience of nature, offering a glimpse into a world untouched by time, a true sanctuary for these remarkable creatures.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_kh3">
        Explore the colorful world with cute clownfish underwater in Taka Bonerate, where the vibrant hues of coral reefs create a mesmerizing backdrop for a diving adventure. Immerse yourself in the beauty of this marine paradise, surrounded by a kaleidoscope of fish and the soothing embrace of the warm, crystal-clear waters of this remote Indonesian archipelago.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_kh4">
        Beware of the stonefish, mysterious creatures lurking in the depths of the ocean, their venomous spines concealed amidst the sandy seabed. With remarkable camouflage abilities, they blend seamlessly into their surroundings, making them formidable predators to unsuspecting prey and a danger to unwary swimmers who may inadvertently disturb their hidden domain.
    </string>
    <string name="tn21_kh5">
        See the mantis shrimp with deadly claws, a top predator in the waters of Taka Bonerate, its iridescent shell shimmering in the sunlight as it swiftly navigates the coral reef, its eyes capable of perceiving colors beyond human imagination, making it a fascinating subject for marine biologists studying its remarkable abilities and adaptations to its environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_a1">
        Enjoy bird watching activities in Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park, where you can witness the diverse array of birds that fill the sky with their vibrant colors and melodious songs. Whether you\'re an avid bird enthusiast or simply appreciate the beauty of nature, this park offers a tranquil setting to observe these magnificent creatures in their natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_a2">
        Embark on a hiking adventure in the midst of the wilderness of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. Enjoy the breathtaking natural scenery, marvel at the diverse wildlife, and explore the lush vegetation. Traverse challenging trails, discover hidden waterfalls, and immerse yourself in the tranquility of nature, making unforgettable memories last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_a3">
        Sail by boat and explore the vibrant and diverse life in the waters of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. A thrilling water adventure awaits, offering breathtaking views of lush landscapes, exotic wildlife, and serene aquatic environments. Experience the magic of nature up close as you navigate through this pristine and enchanting Rawa Aopa national park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_a4">
        Follow the beautiful hiking trails in Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. Enjoy the freshness of nature and the amazing environment, where the lush greenery, diverse wildlife, and tranquil surroundings provide a perfect escape from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. Immerse yourself in the serene atmosphere and experience the natural beauty of this park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_a5">
        Experience a camping adventure in the wilds of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. Enjoy a peaceful night under the starry sky, surrounded by the soothing sounds of nature. Witness the breathtaking sunrise, explore diverse wildlife, and immerse yourself in the pristine beauty of the landscape. Create unforgettable memories as you connect with nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_kh1">
        The cheerful cockatoo, with its vibrant plumage and playful demeanor, stands out as one of the rare and enchanting inhabitants of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. As you explore this paradise, take a moment to witness the beauty of this lovely bird world, where nature\'s wonders unfold in a symphony of colors, sounds, and sights that captivate the soul.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_kh2">
        The Timor deer, a graceful and enchanting creature, contributes to the rich tapestry of biodiversity that defines the splendor of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park. As you venture through the park\'s forests, take a moment to observe these elegant deer, gracefully moving amidst the verdant foliage, adding a touch of natural beauty to this protected sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_kh3">
        The Maleo, a unique and rare bird endemic to Sulawesi, Indonesia, has made Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park its home, where its distinctive presence adds to the allure of this protected area. The park, characterized by lush tropical forests and diverse wildlife, offers visitors the chance to witness the Maleo\'s fascinating nesting behavior and region\'s beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn22_kh4">
        The Tarsius, a charming small primate, is one of the wonders of Rawa Aopa Watumohai National Park, nestled in the verdant landscapes of Indonesia. With their endearing antics and wide-eyed curiosity, these tiny creatures captivate observers as they navigate their natural habitat, offering a glimpse into the enchanting world of wildlife conservation.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_a1">
        Explore the rich native culture in Bajo Mola Village, nestled amid the stunning beauty of Wakatobi National Park. Immerse yourself in the vibrant traditions of the region as you engage with the warm and welcoming local residents, who graciously share their customs and hospitality, creating unforgettable memories of cultural exchange and connection.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_a2">
        Explore the breathtaking beauty of Wakatobi National Park\'s underwater realm through an array of immersive diving experiences, where a mesmerizing marine ecosystem teems with diverse species and showcases awe-inspiring coral reefs, inviting adventurers to delve into an enchanting world beneath the waves and discover the wonders that lie beneath the surface.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_a3">
        Take a paragliding flight and enjoy the breathtaking aerial views in Wakatobi National Park, where the azure waters meet lush greenery, creating a picturesque landscape that stirs the soul. An unforgettable aerial adventure awaits, offering a thrilling journey through the boundless skies, immersing you in nature\'s beauty and serenity like never before.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_a4">
        Bathe in the Kontamale Springs of Wakatobi National Park, where the cooling waters cascade gently, offering a soothing embrace amidst the verdant embrace of nature. Let the tranquil atmosphere envelop you as you unwind in this idyllic setting, surrounded by lush greenery and the calming sounds of cascading waterfalls, a perfect retreat for relaxation.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_a5">
        Toliamba Peak in Wakatobi National Park offers a stunning view from the top, with its lush greenery, vibrant coral reefs, and crystal-clear waters stretching out in all directions, creating a picturesque landscape that captivates the senses and leaves a lasting impression of the natural beauty found in this remote and unspoiled corner of the world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_kh1">
        Witness the captivating school of barracuda in the crystal-clear waters of Wakatobi National Park, where every sleek silhouette dances in harmony, a mesmerizing spectacle of aquatic grace. This underwater realm unveils astonishing sea beauty beneath the surface, a kaleidoscope of colors and life that enchants and inspires all who dare to explore its depths.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_kh2">
        The hawksbill sea turtle, with its intricate shell and graceful movements, is a beloved and vital part of the marine ecosystem within Wakatobi National Park. Their presence, though rare, adds a magical allure to the waters, captivating visitors and scientists alike with their beauty and ecological importance, making them a true treasure of the park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_kh3">
        The Oriolus chinensis bird, adorned with vibrant plumage, gracefully enhances the serene ambiance of Wakatobi National Park with its enchanting melodies, resonating through the tranquil landscape, weaving a symphony of tranquility that captivates all who wander amidst its verdant embrace, their soothing voices becoming the soundtrack of this idyllic sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_kh4">
        The parupeneus cyclostomus fish, with its vibrant hues and graceful movements, serves as a living canvas, enriching the kaleidoscopic tapestry of Wakatobi National Park\'s underwater realm. Its presence underscores the park\'s status as a haven for marine biodiversity, captivating divers and researchers alike with its intricate ecosystems and myriad species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn23_kh5">
        The green turtle, a rare inhabitant of Wakatobi National Park, embodies the delicate balance of marine ecosystems. It is crucial to preserve these magnificent creatures, allowing future generations to witness their beauty and uniqueness as they gracefully navigate the clear waters, highlighting the importance of conservation efforts in sustaining our world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_a1">
        Create unforgettable memories by camping in Lore Lindu National Park, where pristine natural surroundings and refreshing, calming air combine to offer an immersive experience in the heart of nature. Explore diverse flora and fauna, trek through lush forests, and immerse yourself in the rich cultural heritage of the region for an adventure unlike any other.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_a2">
        Discover hidden history at the Tokalaea statue in Lore Lindu National Park, an ancient heritage that reveals stories of the past, offering a glimpse into the rich cultural tapestry of Indonesia, showcasing the intricate craftsmanship of its creators, and inviting visitors to ponder the mysteries and marvels of bygone eras, all set amidst the beauty of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_a3">
        Explore the beauty of the Napu Valley in Lore Lindu National Park, a magnificent landscape boasting lush forests, majestic mountains, and soothing river streams. Immerse yourself in the tranquility of nature as you hike through its pristine trails, marvel at its diverse flora and fauna, and discover the rich cultural heritage of the indigenous communities.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_a4">
        Witness the wonders of the ancient Pokekea archaeological site in Lore Lindu National Park, where traces of an ancient civilization are still alive, whispering stories of the past through intricate stone carvings, towering monuments, and the enigmatic aura of a bygone era, inviting you to unravel the mysteries of their history buried beneath the nature\'s beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_a5">
        Explore the rich tapestry of local culture in Toro Village, nestled amidst the breathtaking landscapes surrounding Lore Lindu National Park. Immerse yourself in the vibrant traditions, savor the flavors of authentic cuisine, and engage with the warm-hearted locals, whose hospitality will leave an indelible mark on your journey through this enchanting world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_kh1">
        The Bubut alang bird is one of the many inhabitants that adorn Lore Lindu National Park, a testament to the park\'s biodiversity. Witness their cheerfulness and activities in the wild, a sight that highlights the delicate balance of nature and the need for conservation efforts to protect such unique species for future generations to admire and cherish.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_kh2">
        Small yet charming, the tarsier is a captivating creature in Lore Lindu National Park, where visitors can witness the resilience and uniqueness of its nocturnal life, marveling at its oversized eyes, which are the largest of any mammal in proportion to its body size, and observing its agile movements as it navigates the dense foliage with remarkable precision.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_kh3">
        The colorful hornbill birds bring their own charm to Lore Lindu National Park, their vibrant feathers and distinctive beaks adding a lively touch to the lush surroundings. Witness the beauty and biodiversity that adorns the sky, where these magnificent creatures soar, reflecting the park\'s rich natural heritage and inviting you to immerse in its wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_kh4">
       The adorable orok-orok\'s behavior, with its playful antics and curious demeanor, serves as a captivating spectacle within the picturesque expanse of Lore Lindu National Park, drawing visitors into the enchanting world of nature\'s wonders. Immerse yourself in their charming antics and cherish these delightful moments throughout your exploration of this journey.
    </string>
    <string name="tn24_kh5">
        The Nepenthes plant, one of the unique plants adorning Lore Lindu National Park, stands out as a natural wonder, holding its own uniqueness among the park\'s diverse flora. Its carnivorous nature, with pitcher-shaped traps, adds to its allure, captivating visitors and botanists, making it a symbol of the park\'s rich biodiversity and ecological significance.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_a1">
        Witness a variety of marine life, including crabs, fish, sea turtles, and colorful coral reefs, inhabiting the crystal-clear waters of Togean, creating a mesmerizing underwater spectacle that attracts divers and nature enthusiasts from around the world, offering a glimpse into the rich biodiversity and natural beauty of this remote Indonesian archipelago.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_a2">
        Explore the beauty of the islands with exciting boat adventures, where you can witness stunning sunsets, discover hidden coves, and enjoy pristine beaches. Navigate through crystal-clear waters, encounter diverse marine life, and create unforgettable memories. Whether you\'re seeking relaxation or adventure, these island boat trips offer memories for everyone.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_a3">
        Dive into the amazing underwater world with diving activities in Togean, where crystal-clear waters, vibrant coral reefs, and diverse marine life await. Explore hidden caves, swim with schools of colorful fish, and discover shipwrecks teeming with history. Togean offers an unforgettable underwater adventure for both novice and experienced divers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_kh1">
        Charmed by the beauty of the \'Red Lionfish\' swimming gracefully in the crystal-clear waters of Togean, I found myself mesmerized by its vibrant colors and delicate fins, moving effortlessly through the coral reefs, creating a breathtaking underwater ballet that captured my heart and left me in awe of nature\'s incredible artistry and the ocean\'s allure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_kh2">
        Explore the underwater world by observing enchanting jellyfish in Togean. Marvel at the graceful movements of these mesmerizing creatures as they drift through the crystal-clear waters, creating an ethereal, dreamlike spectacle. The vibrant marine life and stunning coral reefs of Togean make it a perfect destination for avid snorkelers and divers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn25_kh3">
        Witness a variety of marine life, including crabs, inhabiting the clear, vibrant waters of the Togean Islands. The diverse ecosystem here is teeming with colorful coral reefs, schools of tropical fish, graceful sea turtles, and playful dolphins, making it a perfect destination for snorkeling, diving, and experiencing the wonders of underwater biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_a1">
        The stunning natural beauty of Boganinani Wartabone National Park is epitomized by Lombongok Waterfall. Cascading down rocky cliffs surrounded by lush greenery, the waterfall creates a serene and picturesque scene. Visitors can enjoy the tranquil atmosphere, the refreshing spray of the water, and the diverse wildlife that thrives in this destination.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_a2">
        When nature presents its beauty with cascading water in Boganinani Wartabone National Park, it creates a breathtaking spectacle. The lush greenery, diverse wildlife, and the serene sound of the waterfall combine to offer an unforgettable experience, inviting visitors to immerse themselves in the tranquil and awe-inspiring environment of this magnificent park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_a3">
        Explore the natural wonders of Boganinani Wartabone National Park, where you can marvel at breathtaking views of lush landscapes, diverse wildlife, and pristine rivers. Whether you\'re hiking through dense forests, bird-watching, or simply enjoying the serene beauty, this park offers an unforgettable experience for nature lovers and adventure seekers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_kh1">
        Anoa, the rare treasure of Bogani Nani Wartabone National Park, captivates wildlife enthusiasts and nature lovers with its elusive presence. This endangered species, resembling a miniature water buffalo, roams the lush forests of the park, embodying the pristine beauty and ecological significance of this protected area in Indonesia, making it a must-see.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_kh2">
        Babirusa, the unique forest guardian in the wilderness of Boganinani Wartabone National Park, roams freely amidst the lush greenery. This remarkable creature, known for its distinctive tusks and agile movements, plays a crucial role in maintaining the ecological balance. Its presence is a testament to the rich biodiversity and natural beauty of the region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn26_kh3">
        Maleo Bocos, with their distinctive orange facial skin and intricate courtship dances, are among the captivating avian inhabitants gracing the lush landscapes of Boganinani Wartabone National Park in Indonesia. Their presence enriches the biodiversity of the park, captivating visitors with their behaviors and contributing to the ecological tapestry of this area.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_a1">
        Relish the tranquil sensation of immersing yourself in the mesmerizing crystal blue waters of Bunaken National Park, where vibrant coral reefs teem with life beneath the sun-dappled surface, creating an enchanting aquatic paradise that beckons adventurers and nature enthusiasts alike to explore its breathtaking beauty and vibrant marine ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_a2">
        Explore the beauty of the underwater world at Bunaken National Park with snorkeling alongside spectacular coral formations, where a kaleidoscope of marine life dances amidst the vibrant hues of the reef. Lose yourself in the tranquility of azure waters teeming with exotic creatures, immersing in an unforgettable adventure beneath the shimmering waves.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_a3">
        Explore the breathtaking beauty of the mesmerizing underwater world as you embark on an unforgettable diving adventure in Bunaken National Park, where you\'ll encounter vibrant coral reefs teeming with diverse marine life. Immerse yourself in the crystal-clear waters of these pristine locations, revealing nature\'s most spectacular wonders beneath the surface.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_a4">
        Embark on an awe-inspiring journey as you witness the diverse beauty of coral reefs thriving within the turquoise waters of Bunaken National Park. Join guided tours that traverse the vibrant reef ecosystems, immersing yourself in an enchanting world where marine life flourishes in breathtaking harmony, leaving indelible memories etched in your soul.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_a5">
        Immerse yourself in the lush biodiversity of Bunaken National Park as you venture through the enchanting mangrove forests, where twisting roots create a labyrinthine sanctuary for diverse marine life. From vibrant coral reefs to hidden coves, every corner beckons exploration, promising an unforgettable journey into the heart of this tropical paradise.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_kh1">
        Charming green turtles, gracefully gliding through the crystalline waters, are just one of the myriad underwater wonders awaiting discovery in the breathtaking expanse of Bunaken National Park, a sanctuary where vibrant marine life dances amidst coral gardens, inviting to immerse themselves in the mesmerizing spectacle of nature beneath the waves.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_kh2">
        Explore the vibrant tapestry of biodiversity, immersing yourself in the intricate ecosystems where every corner unveils fascinating creatures like the graceful copperband butterflyfish, adorned with its striking bands of color, a testament to the endless wonders awaiting discovery beneath the shimmering surface of our planet\'s diverse aquatic realms.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_kh3">
        Dugongs, the rare and majestic sea icons of Bunaken National Park, gracefully swim in the crystal-clear waters with us, their elegant movements mirroring the tranquility of this pristine marine sanctuary, as we marvel at their ethereal presence, awestruck by the delicate harmony between these gentle giants and the vibrant aquatic ecosystem surrounding them.
    </string>
    <string name="tn27_kh4">
        The underwater mystery unfolds as the graceful coral reef snake, with its vibrant scales shimmering under the gentle caress of sunlight filtering through the azure waters, elegantly maneuvers among the intricate labyrinth of colorful coral reefs, each teeming with life, revealing the mesmerizing tapestry of nature\'s beauty hidden beneath the waves.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_a1">
        Glide with the wind in the enchanting waters of Ujung Kulon, where the pristine waves and vibrant marine life create a paradise for adventurers. Nestled on the western tip of Java, this hidden gem offers a breathtaking blend of turquoise waters, lush jungles, and serene beaches, making it the perfect escape for nature lovers and thrill-seekers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_a2">
        At Panaitan Beach, surfing enthusiasts can ride the big waves, feeling the exhilarating rush of adrenaline as they challenge themselves against the powerful ocean swells. The experience of surfing at this location is sure to be unforgettable, offering an opportunity to connect with nature and test your skills in a thrilling and dynamic environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_a3">
        As the divers gear up with their wetsuits, oxygen tanks, and flippers, they eagerly anticipate plunging beneath the shimmering surface of the offshore waters surrounding Ujung Kulon. Ready to explore the mysteries hidden in the aquatic realm, they stand poised on the edge of the boat, their hearts filled with excitement for the adventure that lies ahead.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_kh1">
        Meet the Javan langur, scientifically known as Trachypithecus auratus, an endemic primate species found in the lush forests of Ujung Kulon National Park, Indonesia. These majestic animals are characterized by their striking black fur and distinctive long tails, making them a significant and captivating sight for visitors exploring the park\'s biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_kh2">
        It is of utmost importance that we take immediate action to safeguard the Javan rhinoceros, a critically endangered species that remains one of the few survivors in this region. Protecting these majestic creatures is essential to preserving the delicate balance of biodiversity and ensuring their survival for future generations to admire and learn from.
    </string>
    <string name="tn28_kh3">
        Experience the mesmerizing sight of herds of wild banteng peacefully grazing and roaming in their untouched natural habitat within the vast expanse of Ujung Kulon National Park. Embrace the opportunity to observe these majestic creatures as they interact with each other and their environment, creating a truly unforgettable wildlife-watching experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_a1">
        Come and create lasting memories by getting up close and personal with adorable young sea turtles at our dedicated conservation facility. Engage in meaningful interactions as you witness these magnificent creatures in their natural habitat, fostering a deeper connection with marine life and contributing to the protection of these endangered species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_a2">
        Immerse yourself in the wondrous depths of the Thousand Islands, where you can explore and discover the mesmerizing worlds beneath the surface, filled with a diverse array of marine life, colorful corals swaying in the gentle currents, and fascinating underwater ecosystems waiting to be admired and appreciated for their natural beauty and splendor.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_a3">
        Immerse yourself in the enchanting beauty of the underwater realm by embarking on a mesmerizing snorkeling adventure in the crystal-clear waters surrounding the archipelago of the Thousand Islands. Explore the vibrant marine life and vibrant coral gardens, creating unforgettable memories as you connect with nature in this stunning aquatic paradise.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_kh1">
        The colorful underwater life with clownfish and their companions creates an amazing view, as vibrant corals sway gently in the current and schools of tropical fish dart around, adding a dynamic energy to the serene marine environment. The symphony of colors and movements in this underwater world paints a breathtaking picture of nature\'s beauty and diversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_kh2">
        The majestic sharp-eyed eagles can often be spotted gracefully soaring through the vast skies of Kepulauan Seribu, exuding a sense of freedom with their powerful wings outstretched as they effortlessly navigate the winds, showcasing their unparalleled hunting skills and keen eyesight that makes them efficient predators within their natural habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn29_kh3">
        The awe-inspiring hawksbill turtles, with their majestic shells glinting under the sun\'s rays, elegantly cut through the crystal-clear waters, providing a captivating glimpse into the diverse and enchanting underwater realm, where a plethora of fascinating marine creatures coexist harmoniously, creating a mesmerizing spectacle for all to behold and cherish.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_a1">
        Immerse yourself in the mesmerizing natural beauty of Mount Halimun Salak as you set up your camp amidst the vibrant greenery of the lush forest. Let the soothing sounds of rustling leaves and chirping birds serenade you as you gaze upon the majestic mountains that stand tall in the distance, forming a picturesque backdrop for your outdoor adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_a2">
        Unwind and elevate your spirits by immersing yourself in the lively tunes of a live music performances under the starlit night sky. Embrace the harmonious melodies and rhythmic beats as you bask in the natural beauty of the outdoors, creating a magical and unforgettable experience that combines the pleasures of music with the serenity of the night.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_a3">
        Embark on a thrilling journey through vibrant landscapes, where you can immerse yourself in the captivating allure of untouched nature. Along the way, the breathtaking "Curug Seribu" waterfall, a sight so majestic that it will leave you spellbound. This is an adventure that promises to be filled with awe-inspiring experiences and unforgettable moments.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_a4">
        Embark on exhilarating and physically demanding treks winding through the awe-inspiring, lush forests teeming with diverse flora and fauna. The challenging paths lead you deep into the heart of nature, providing an invigorating experience as you navigate through the verdant landscape, filled with hidden gems waiting to be discovered and appreciated.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_kh1">
        The footprints of the clouded leopard, a majestic and elusive creature, can often be spotted among the dense foliage and towering trees that grace the landscape of Mount Halimun Salak National Park. These subtle imprints in the earth tell stories of stealthy movements and natural grace, adding to the park\'s allure as a sanctuary for diverse wildlife.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_kh2">
        In this untouched wilderness, venture into the serene surroundings to observe the Javan gibbon, a critically endangered and rare primate species, gracefully moving through the lush greenery of its native habitat. Experience the unique opportunity to witness these rare creatures up close and admire their agility and elegance in their natural environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn30_kh3">
       Beautiful orchids, with their vibrant colors and delicate petals, add a touch of elegance to the diverse array of plant life thriving in the lush forests of Mount Halimun Salak. These graceful flowers, gracefully swaying in the gentle mountain breeze, are a testament to the rich biodiversity and natural beauty that characterize this captivating landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_a1">
        Trekking through the dense mossy forests on your way to the peak of Mount Gede is an enchanting experience. As you reach the summit, the majestic mountain Cantigi stands tall, creating a stunning backdrop. One cannot help but be captivated by the natural beauty of Mount Gede, especially the breathtaking bed of Edelweiss flowers that blankets the landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_a2">
        Experience a sense of peace and serenity as you bask in the tranquil beauty of Situgunung Lake nestled within the lush landscapes of Gede Pangrango National Park. This serene oasis provides the perfect setting for unwinding and immersing yourself in the stunning vistas that surround you, creating an idyllic escape from the hustle and bustle of daily life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_a3">
        Dive into an unforgettable adventure in the breathtaking Gede Pangrango National Park as you explore the tranquil beauty of Curug Luhur, a majestic waterfall nestled amidst lush greenery. Immerse yourself in the refreshing natural surroundings to truly appreciate the wonders while experiencing a sense of peace and serenity that this hidden gem offers.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_a4">
        Immerse yourself in the serene embrace of nature by booking a getaway at the New Bolang Campground located in the heart of the Gede Pangrango National Park. Here, you can enjoy a delightful camping adventure surrounded by the vibrant greenery of the lush forest, creating a truly peaceful and rejuvenating experience amidst the beauty of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_a5">
        Embark on a mesmerizing journey through the lush greenery of the forest on the Canopy Trail Ciwalen in the breathtaking Gede Pangrango National Park. As you hike among the towering trees and wildlife, you\'ll be greeted with a panoramic view that showcases the awe-inspiring beauty of the natural world, leaving you in awe of the wonders that surround you.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_kh1">
        Embark on a breathtaking adventure through the lush forest by walking along the Canopy Trail Ciwalen within the Gede Pangrango National Park. This journey allows you to ascend to towering heights and immerse yourself in the mesmerizing beauty of the natural world, offering a truly spectacular vista that showcases the awe-inspiring wonders of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_kh2">
        The lush forests of the Gede Pangrango Complex provide a rich hunting ground for the majestic Javan leopard, showcasing a diverse array of this feline species including the elusive clouded leopard and the distinctively marked spotted leopard, each adding a layer of exotic beauty and mystery to the natural landscape captured in the accompanying picture.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_kh3">
        Amidst the vibrant green leaves and thick foliage of the lush forest canopy, the agile Javan Gibbon (Hylobates moloch) can be seen springing gracefully from one tree to another, effortlessly navigating through the dense vegetation with its incredible agility and remarkable precision, reminding us of the beauty and harmony of nature\'s intricate ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_kh4">
        Visitors to the Gede Pangrango National Park are enchanted by the astounding beauty of the rare and endemic plant species known as Raflesia Rochussenii. This magnificent flower captivates observers with its vibrant colours and unique features, making it a must-see attraction for nature enthusiasts exploring this biodiverse and pristine environment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn31_kh5">
        As the morning gradually unfolds its splendor, the gentle rays of the rising sun gracefully intertwine with the glistening dew adorning the majestic Cantigi and Edelweiss peaks, creating a picturesque scene that etches vivid memories in the hearts of all who venture to Mount Gede Pangrango, beckoning them to return and bask in the natural beauty once more.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_a1">
        Embark on an exhilarating natural journey through the rugged terrain of Ciremai Mountain National Park, where you can immerse yourself in the wonders of the wilderness. Challenge yourself by exploring the winding trails that will lead you to breathtaking viewpoints and unique flora and fauna, making your trek a truly memorable and rewarding experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_a2">
        At the foot of majestic Ciremai Mountain, visitors can delight in the revitalizing splashes of waterfalls cascading down the rugged terrain, creating a sense of serenity and awe-inspiring beauty in the surrounding landscape. The crystal-clear waters provide a refreshing respite for adventurous hikers and nature enthusiasts exploring this picturesque region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_a3">
        Delight in the serene experience of swimming in the midst of nature, accompanied by the revered sacred fish that hold a special place within the tight-knit Kuningan community. Feel a profound connection with the environment as you glide through the water, surrounded by these mystical creatures that embody the spirituality and harmony cherished by the locals.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_kh1">
        The sleek and powerful species, black panther, fearlessly prowls through the dense, shadowy forests, venturing into the uncharted territories that hold untold secrets and beauty within the heart of the natural world, where mysterious wonders and dangers intertwine to create a realm of awe-inspiring discoveries waiting to be unraveled by the fearless feline.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_kh2">
        In the lush greenery of Ciremai Mountain National Park, the adorable slow loris can be seen leaping with graceful agility, its fur shimmering in the sunlight. The playful antics of this charming creature create a delightful sight for visitors exploring the park\'s natural beauty and diverse wildlife, adding a touch of whimsy to the serene mountain landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_kh3">
        The unforgettable beauty of the Nine O\'Clock flower in the Ciremai Mountain National Park enchants visitors with its delicate petals that bloom in radiant hues, casting a mesmerizing glow against the backdrop of lush greenery and mist-covered peaks, creating a breathtaking sight that leaves a lasting impression on all who are fortunate enough to witness it.
    </string>
    <string name="tn32_kh4">
        Edelweiss, known for its delicate white petals, elegantly embellishes the picturesque landscapes of the stunning Ciremai Mountain National Park, creating a breathtaking sight that captures the essence of untamed natural beauty and charm, making it a beloved attraction for nature enthusiasts and visitors seeking serenity amidst the rugged wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_a1">
        Breathtakingly beautiful coral reefs, with their intricate formations and vibrant colors, provide a mesmerizing underwater environment for divers and snorkelers alike. Delicate sea creatures, from shimmering schools of fish to graceful sea turtles, add to the allure of the marine world waiting to be discovered beneath the crystal-clear blue waters.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_a2">
        Indulge in the delectable flavors of traditional local dishes, carefully prepared to delight and excite your taste buds during your time in Karimun Jawa. Whether you crave the fiery kick of sambal or the rich aroma of freshly caught seafood, Karimun Jawa island will offer you a culinary experience that will surely leave your palate longing for more.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_a3">
        Immerse yourself in the enigmatic depths of the sea, where every dive unveils a mesmerizing world filled with spectacular marine life, stunning coral reefs, and hidden wonders waiting to be explored. Discover the ethereal beauty that lies beneath the surface as you embark on an unforgettable journey through the vast and intriguing underwater realm.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_kh1">
        Clams in Karimun Jawa National Park, with their mesmerizing shells glittering under the sunlight, play a crucial role in maintaining the delicate balance of the marine ecosystem by quietly filtering the mysteries and wonders of the sea, extracting nutrients and impurities with meticulous precision, thereby contributing to the park\'s richness and diversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_kh2">
        A playful clownfish, with vibrant orange and white stripes that shimmer under the sunlight, gracefully glides among the colorful coral reefs, injecting a sense of joy and wonder into the crystal-clear waters of the majestic Karimun Jawa National Park, creating a mesmerizing spectacle that delights both wildlife enthusiasts and casual visitors alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_kh3">
        A playful clownfish, with vibrant orange and white stripes that shimmer under the sunlight, gracefully glides among the colorful coral reefs, injecting a sense of joy and wonder into the crystal-clear waters of the majestic Karimun Jawa National Park, creating a mesmerizing spectacle that delights both wildlife enthusiasts and casual visitors alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_kh4">
        Seagulls gracefully soar above the turquoise waters, their wings glinting in the sun\'s golden rays, performing an elegant ballet in the endless blue sky, a sight that mesmerizes all who visit the tranquil shores of Karimun Jawa as these majestic birds dutifully watch over the pristine coasts, adding a touch of natural splendor to the island paradise.
    </string>
    <string name="tn33_kh5">
        Humble sea cucumbers, with their unassuming presence, play a vital role in maintaining the delicate balance of the marine ecosystem in the pristine waters of Karimun Jawa. These remarkable creatures silently support the biodiversity of the area, serving as essential contributors to the overall health and sustainability of the underwater world around them.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_a1">
        Have an exhilarating experience by enjoying a night under the sparkling stars, then wake up refreshed and invigorated at the base of the majestic Mount Merbabu after spending the night camping. Embrace the tranquility of the early morning as you greet the sunrise amidst the beauty of nature surrounding you, creating unforgettable memories to cherish.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_a2">
        Embark on a fascinating journey of discovery as you immerse yourself in the vibrant local culture, gaining insight into the traditions, and way of life of the nearby inhabitants. Delve deep into their daily routines, savoring the authentic experiences and interactions that will enrich your understanding and appreciation of the community\'s unique identity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_a3">
        Embark on a thrilling adventure as you challenge yourself with a demanding trek through the awe-inspiring and majestic peaks of Mount Merbabu. The journey promises not only physical exertion as you conquer steep trails and rocky terrain, but also endless opportunities to immerse yourself in the breathtaking natural beauty surrounding this iconic mountain.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_kh1">
        The surili, with its endearing and playful expressions, captures the hearts of all who encounter it on the awe-inspiring Mount Merbabu. These charming creatures, known for their distinct and lovable features, add a touch of whimsy and enchantment to the already breathtaking landscape of the mountain, making it an unforgettable experience for visitors.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_kh2">
        Immerse yourself in the vibrant world of the lively monkey community as you venture through the breathtaking natural landscapes of Mount Merbabu. Experience the playful interactions and curious antics of the monkeys as they inhabit this picturesque environment, adding an element of excitement and charm to your exploration of this stunning mountain region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn34_kh3">
        In addition to being home to furry creatures like foxes and squirrels, Mount Merbabu is also a haven for various exotic plants such as the rare Waldsteinia. Its lush vegetation provides a diverse ecosystem, fostering the growth of unique flora that thrive in the mountain\'s pristine environment, creating a harmonious balance in its natural landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_a1">
        Embark on thrilling offroad adventures along the rugged slopes of Mount Merapi, where the adrenaline rush of navigating the challenging terrain with powerful off road vehicles awaits. Experience the excitement of conquering steep inclines and rough paths, immersing yourself in the natural beauty and thrill of the journey up one of the most iconic volcanoes
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_a2">
        Embark on an awe-inspiring journey to discover the rich and varied birdlife thriving within the breathtaking landscapes of Mount Merapi National Park. Immerse yourself in the vibrant ecosystem and witness a diverse bird species, from colorful songbirds to majestic birds of prey, making this park a paradise for bird enthusiasts and nature lovers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_a3">
        Cycle through the lush and vibrant nature of Mount Merapi to fully immerse yourself in a rejuvenating and invigorating experience that will refresh your body, soul, and sense. Embrace the breathtaking scenery and feel the crisp mountain air as you pedal through this stunning landscape, connecting with the beauty of nature in a truly exhilarating way.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_kh1">
        The Javan Hawk-Eagle, a magnificent bird known as the ruler of Mount Merapi\'s skies due to its impressive wingspan and keen eyesight, gracefully navigates the currents above the rugged mountain slopes. Its majestic presence evokes a sense of power and freedom, symbolizing the untamed beauty of the natural world in this breathtaking landscape of Mount Merapi.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_kh2">
        Witness the majestic Bido snake eagle as it soars gracefully through the skies of Mount Merapi, showcasing its unparalleled hunting skills and asserting its dominance as the top predator in the region. Its impressive aerial maneuvers and keen predatory instincts make it a truly awe-inspiring sight to behold, symbolizing the power and beauty of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_kh3">
        Indulge in the delightful sweetness of Sriganti honey, a truly exquisite and rejuvenating natural creation sourced from the magnificent Mount Merapi. This honey, with its rich and flavorful taste, promises to be a delightful treat for your taste buds, offering a unique and refreshing experience that captures the essence of nature\'s finest offerings.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_kh4">
        The exotic Vanda Tricolor orchid, characterized by its vibrant hues of purple and white, is a natural charm that decorates the rugged slopes of Mount Merapi, creating a stunning contrast against the volcanic terrain. Its delicate petals sway gracefully in the mountain breeze, adding a touch of elegance to the wild landscape of this majestic volcano.
    </string>
    <string name="tn35_kh5">
        The Purple-headed Lizard, scientifically known as Iguana violacea, is a visually stunning reptile species that can be found gracefully moving through the rugged terrain surrounding the majestic Mount Merapi. With its distinctive purple hue and intricate patterns adorning its scales, this special lizard exemplifies the diverse beauty of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_a1">
        Witness the breathtaking beauty of a diverse array of exotic birds as they elegantly gather at the foot of the majestic mountain, their vibrant plumage creating a stunning contrast against the natural backdrop. The colorful symphony of chirps and calls fills the air, creating a mesmerizing spectacle that captivates all who have the opportunity to witness it.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_a2">
        Immerse yourself in the thrill of nature by venturing through rugged and demanding hiking trails that lead you to breathtaking vistas and reveal spectacular landscapes at every turn. Experience the exhilaration of conquering obstacles while being rewarded with awe-inspiring views that will surely leave you in awe with each adventurous stride taken.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_a3">
        Delve into the serene tranquility of nature as you leisurely embark on horseback riding adventures, smoothly gliding through breathtaking landscapes that captivate the soul with their endless beauty, offering a unique way to connect with the natural world and experience a sense of freedom as you immerse yourself in the wonders of the great outdoors.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_kh1">
        The towering view of the Javan Hawk-Eagle, a majestic and rare bird of prey, overseeing its expansive territory from the heights of Mount Bromo Tengger Semeru, is a sight to behold. This critically endangered species, with its striking plumage and keen eyesight, symbolizes the wild beauty and ecological diversity of this iconic Indonesian landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_kh2">
        The Jelarang, a playful and agile tree-dwelling creature, frolics freely in the midst of the lush forest canopy. With its vibrant fur and lively antics, it leaps from branch to branch, bringing a sense of joy and vitality to the serene wilderness. Observing this delightful animal is a reminder of the rich biodiversity that thrives in the heart of the forest.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_kh3">
        Greet the cheerful group of Javan Langurs as they energetically play among the lush trees. These agile and social primates, with their distinctive black and orange fur, leap gracefully from one branch to another, chattering and interacting in a display of their lively and vibrant community within the rich and diverse forests of their Javanese homeland.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_kh4">
        The enchantment of the spotted Panthera pardus melas, also known as the Javan leopard, prowling through the dense, shadowy forest at night is a mesmerizing sight. This elusive and endangered predator moves with a grace and stealth that epitomizes the mystery and allure of the nocturnal wilderness, embodying the untamed spirit of its jungle habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn36_kh5">
       A rare moment capturing the male Lacedo Pulchella, commonly known as the blue-crowned rock thrush, in action in the wild is truly mesmerizing. With its vibrant blue crown and striking plumage, this elusive bird, usually hidden within dense forests, is caught mid-flight, showcasing its natural grace and the breathtaking beauty of its untamed habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_a1">
        Enjoy the fun waves with bodyboarding on the beautiful beach of Meru Betiri National Park. Experience the exciting sensation of riding the rolling sea waves, feeling the rush of adrenaline as you navigate each crest and trough, making for a thrilling and unforgettable holiday experience amidst the stunning natural beauty of this coastal paradise for you.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_a2">
        Relax with a serene canoe trip in Meru Betiri National Park, where you can leisurely paddle through pristine waters surrounded by lush tropical rainforests. As you explore the tranquil waterways, immerse yourself in the breathtaking beauty of nature, encountering diverse wildlife and vibrant flora, all while enjoying the peaceful sounds of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_a3">
        Travelers can express their affection by burying turtle eggs in the hatchery, where they are nurtured until hatching. Once emerged, the adorable hatchlings scatter within the hatchery, receiving dedicated care. Upon maturity, they are tenderly released back into the pristine expanse of Sukamade Beach, fostering the conservation of these beloved creatures.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_a4">
        Sukamade\'s charm elevates this beach to prominence, earning it a coveted spot in the diamond triangle destination promoted jointly by the Banyuwangi Regency government and the Meru Betiri National Park Office. With its pristine shores and rich biodiversity, Sukamade beckons travelers seeking unspoiled natural beauty and immersive wildlife experiences.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_a5">
        Bandelit Beach, nestled on Java Island\'s eastern coast, captivates with its serene charm. Golden sands meet azure waters, inviting tranquility seekers to indulge in the rhythmic symphony of crashing waves. Surrounded by lush greenery, this coastal gem offers a retreat into nature\'s embrace, beckoning visitors to unwind amidst its picturesque vistas.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_kh1">
        Nestled amidst Java\'s urban density, Meru Betiri stands as a bastion of serenity and conservation, bearing the vital responsibility of protecting endangered sea turtles. Amidst the hustle and bustle of human activity, this sanctuary offers a tranquil refuge, fostering the preservation of these majestic marine creatures for future generations to admire.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_kh2">
        The leopard, renowned as one of the apex predators in the intricate ecosystem of these dense forests, plays a crucial role in regulating prey populations, thus maintaining the delicate balance of the ecosystem. With its stealth, agility, and formidable hunting prowess, the leopard embodies the raw power and resilience of nature\'s intricate web of life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_kh3">
        Nestled within the untamed expanse of the Meru Betiri wilderness lies sanctuary for the Javan Hawk Eagle (Nisaetus bartelsi), an endemic and revered bird of prey native to the rugged landscapes of Java. With its imposing presence and aerial prowess, this magnificent creature epitomizes the rich biodiversity and natural splendor of this remote region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_kh4">
        Immerse yourself in the enchanting world of Meru Betiri National Park and view the lively antics of its gray macaques. These cheerful forest residents are sure to bring joy to your journey as they playfully roam their natural habitat. Don\'t miss the opportunity to experience the exuberance of these delightful creatures amidst the serene beauty of the park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn37_kh5">
        One of the phenomenal plants, Padmosari (Rafflesia zollingeriana), with its mesmerizing, oversized blooms, can still be encountered by the public within this conservation area. This rare species, known for its distinctive foul odor and remarkable size, adds to the allure and biodiversity of the region, captivating visitors with its unique presence.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_a1">
        Discover the serene beauty of the lake by embarking on a thrilling kayaking expedition in Gunung Gede Pangrango National Park. This exhilarating water escapade promises excitement for all adventure enthusiasts, offering a unique opportunity to immerse yourself in nature\'s splendor while navigating the tranquil waters of the park\'s picturesque lake.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_a2">
        Explore the wonderful and captivating underwater world through snorkeling at the stunning beaches of Baluran National Park. Immerse yourself in the wonders of marine life, encountering vibrant coral reefs and a myriad of colorful fish species. Discover the magic beneath the waves as you witness the beauty and biodiversity of this remarkable marine ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_a3">
        Enjoy a delightful journey horseback riding through the scenic landscapes of Baluran National Park. As you traverse the vast savannah, you\'ll experience the refreshing natural beauty and unique wildlife of this remarkable area, often referred to as the "Little Africa" of Java Island. The park\'s diverse ecosystems offer a truly unforgettable adventure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_a4">
        Witness the breathtaking panorama of Bekol savannah in Baluran National Park Situbondo, where the vast natural beauty stretches out before you. The enchanting views of the sprawling savannah, teeming with diverse wildlife and framed by majestic mountains, create an unforgettable scene that captures the essence of Indonesia\'s rich ecological heritage.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_a5">
        Relax and enjoy the unparalleled beauty of Bama Beach in Baluran National Park. The pristine white sand and crystal-clear waters create an inviting paradise, perfect for a serene escape. Whether you\'re sunbathing, swimming, diving, or simply taking in the stunning natural surroundings, Bama Beach promises a rejuvenating and unforgettable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_kh1">
        Another easily spotted wildlife is the Green Peafowl (Pavo muticus), particularly during their mating season from July to November. Before dawn breaks, the resonant calls of the male peafowls shatter the pre-dawn silence, inviting responses from the females. This vibrant display of courtship behavior is a captivating experience for any wildlife enthusiast.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_kh2">
        Witness the mesmerizing beauty of Baluran National Park\'s untamed wilderness through the vibrant presence of the green junglefowl. These striking bird are an inseparable part of the rich biodiversity thriving within this lush forest, symbolizing the ecological complexity and natural splendor that make this national park a true haven for wildlife enthusiasts.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_kh3">
        At Baluran National Park, playful squirrels scamper through the trees, their bushy tails a flash of brown against the green. These cheeky critters, always full of energy, will often dart out from behind a trunk or peek down from a branch, their bright eyes sparkling with curiosity. Don\'t be surprised if they approach you playfully, hoping for a tasty treat!
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_kh4">
        In the Bekol savannah, a diverse array of wildlife, such as the Wild Buffalo (Bubalus bubalis), can be spotted grazing. These magnificent creatures are often found congregating near the scattered water holes, showcasing their resilience in adapting to the arid landscape. Their presence adds vibrancy to the ecosystem, reflecting the balance of life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn38_kh5">
        In the expansive Bekol savannah, one can spot a diverse array of wildlife, such as the graceful Timor Deer (Cervus timorensis), peacefully grazing near the scattered water holes. These deer, abundant in this ecosystem, add to the natural charm of this picturesque landscape, offering a glimpse into the harmonious coexistence of creatures within their habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_a1">
        Dive into the invigorating waves of Alas Purwo and experience the pure joy of swimming in it. Surrounded by pristine beaches and lush greenery, this tranquil oasis offers a rejuvenating escape from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. Immerse yourself in the natural beauty of this coastal paradise and let the rhythmic motion of the waves soothe your soul.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_a2">
        Immerse yourself in the vibrant tapestry of indigenous traditions set against breathtaking natural landscapes. Journey through centuries-old customs and rituals intertwined with the lush beauty of the surroundings. Explore the intricate connections between people and their environment, as ancient heritage unfolds in harmony with the serene wonders of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_a3">
        Surfers eagerly anticipate the perfect waves off the coast of Plengkung. Gliding along the wave walls atop their surfboards, they\'re enveloped in an unforgettable sensation. This fusion of adrenaline and serenity etches indelible memories. Amidst breathtaking natural beauty, immerse yourself in the local culture, a journey brimming with authenticity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_kh1">
        In the heart of Alas Purwo National Park, amidst the lush wilderness, stands the majestic buffalo, a symbol of raw natural power. Its imposing figure commands respect, embodying the untamed essence of the wild. With every powerful stride, it reaffirms the park\'s status as a sanctuary where nature reigns supreme, untouched by the hands of civilization.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_kh2">
        Observe the enchanting spectacle of the long-tailed macaques frolicking amidst the lush canopy of trees, their playful antics weaving an exquisite tapestry within the vibrant ecosystem of this revered national park. These agile primates contribute to the rich tapestry of natural ecosystem that thrives harmoniously within this pristine sanctuary of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_kh3">
        In Alas Purwo National Park, Bali, the serene expanse of grasslands plays host to wandering cattle, adding to the tranquil ambiance of the landscape. Against the backdrop of untouched nature, these roaming herds contribute to the park\'s picturesque charm, offering visitors a glimpse into the harmonious coexistence between wildlife and pastoral scenes.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_kh4">
       In the embrace of the natural world, graceful peacocks flaunt their vibrant plumage, painting the skies with hues of azure and emerald. Their elegance enchants, a symphony of beauty in flight, as they dance upon the canvas of nature, their feathers unfurling like delicate strokes of an artist\'s brush, adding a touch of ethereal charm to the serene landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn39_kh5">
        Roaming deer, with their graceful strides and gentle demeanor, symbolize the untouched wilderness of Alas Purwo. Their presence not only adds to the scenic beauty but also indicates a thriving ecosystem. As they move through the dense forests and open meadow, they contribute to the delicate balance of nature, embodying the essence of this pristine sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_a1">
        Immerse yourself in the enchanting allure of the dense forest, where every step unveils a new encounter with fascinating wildlife. From the majestic canopy to the bustling forest floor, nature\'s wonders await your discovery. Venture forth and let the serene beauty of the wilderness captivate your senses, creating memories that will last a lifetime.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_a2">
        Relax and bask in the warmth of the sun as you stretch out on the pristine white sands of Teluk Terima Beach. Let the gentle rhythm of the waves serenade you, transporting you to a state of tranquil bliss. Indulge in the perfect harmony of nature\'s beauty and the calming melody of the sea, creating timeless moments of pure relaxation and rejuvenation.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_a3">
        Experience the captivating allure of Balinese cu lture as you immerse yourself in the richness of its spiritual tapestry through deeply meaningful religious ceremonies. From intricate rituals to vibrant festivals, every moment resonates with the essence of Balinese tradition, offering a profound glimpse into the soul of this enchanting island paradise.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_kh1">
        Delight in the mesmerizing spectacle as vibrant clownfish dart and weave through intricate coral formations, their brilliant hues contrasting against the vivid backdrop of the reef. Behold their playful antics as they gracefully navigate their underwater world, a testament to nature\'s boundless creativity and the delicate balance of marine ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_kh2">
        Witness the exquisite beauty of the rare Bali myna bird as it thrives in its untouched natural habitat. Its elegant plumage and graceful demeanor captivate all who witness the bird. In the lush forests of Bali, this avian wonder dances among the foliage, a symbol of the precious biodiversity that must be cherished and protected for generations to come.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_kh3">
        Experience the enchanting allure of the Bali starling bird as it gracefully roams the untamed landscapes of West Bali. Immerse yourself in the beauty of nature as you observe these majestic creatures in their natural habitat, their pure white feathers contrasting against the lush greenery, creating a scene of unparalleled serenity and wonder for the witness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_kh4">
        As the golden sun dips below the horizon, casting long shadows across the vast national park, embark on a quest to find the elusive red-backed kingfisher. With each step on the trail, breathe in the crisp air and soak in the vibrant tapestry of nature. Keep your eyes peeled for a flash of red-backed kingfisher dazzling plumage against the fiery sunset.
    </string>
    <string name="tn40_kh5">
        Set out on a thrilling expedition through the lush forests of West Bali, where you\'ll have the chance to come face-to-face with wild boars, wandering freely amidst the verdant landscape. Experience the adrenaline rush as you navigate the untamed terrain, immersing yourself in the raw beauty of nature while encountering these magnificent creatures up close.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_a1">
        Embarking on an unforgettable camping journey beneath the mesmerizing star-studded canopy of Mount Rinjani, where each twinkling star seems to whisper ancient secrets. Enveloped by the gentle melodies of nature, one finds solace in the rhythmic symphony of rustling leaves and distant wildlife, forging an unparalleled connection with the untamed wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_a2">
        Embark on an exhilarating adventure to the mountain peak, where every step unveils the breathtaking panorama of Mount Rinjani National Park. Traverse rugged terrains and conquer heights to behold the awe-inspiring beauty of nature\'s masterpiece. With each ascent, immerse yourself in the serenity of the wilderness while embracing the thrill of exploration.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_a3">
        Cast your line into the tranquil waters of the river flowing gracefully amidst the breathtaking allure of Mount Rinjani. Feel the gentle breeze as you wait for a fish to be bait, surrounded by the serene ambiance of nature\'s masterpiece. Discover the joy of fishing amidst such captivating scenery, where every moment is a treasure waiting to be found.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_kh1">
        Marvel at the exquisite Rinjani scops owls as it gracefully spreads its majestic wings across the expansive sky, a captivating sight within the breathtaking landscape of this national park. Encounter the allure of nature as you observe this magnificent creature in its natural habitat, an experience that immerses you in the wonder of the wilderness.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_kh2">
        Eagles gracefully navigate the boundless expanse above Mount Rinjani, a majestic peak intertwined with the web of its ecosystem. With keen eyesight, they survey the landscape, embodying the essence of freedom amidst the rugged terrain. Their presence enriches the mountain\'s allure, symbolizing resilience and harmony within nature\'s intricate tapestry.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_kh3">
        In the heart of Mount Rinjani National Park, where lush forests thrive, wild deer gracefully traverse, enhancing the rich tapestry of biodiversity. Their presence symbolizes the delicate balance of nature, contributing to the park\'s ecological harmony and captivating visitors with the enchanting sight of these majestic creatures amidst the verdant landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn41_kh4">
        The pangolin, a treasured inhabitant of this national park, wanders amidst the lush foliage, a testament to the park\'s biodiversity. With its distinctive scales and elusive nature, encountering a pangolin in its natural habitat is a rare and unforgettable experience, underscoring the park\'s commitment to conservation and preservation of endangered species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_a1">
        Embark on an adventure to explore the rugged terrains of Komodo National Park. Trek through majestic mountains, immerse yourself in the untouched beauty of nature, and forge a deep connection with the wild. Encounter the iconic Komodo dragons and experience the raw wilderness like never before. Komodo National Park awaits, promising an unforgettable journey.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_a2">
        Observe the awe-inspiring Komodo dragons in their natural habitat, where these formidable creatures roam freely on the rugged, picturesque islands of Indonesia. Witness their sheer power and agility as they navigate the diverse terrain, a rare and unforgettable experience that offers a glimpse into the lives of these ancient, big, and majestic reptiles.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_a3">
        Venture underwater and explore the spectacular marine world around Komodo National Park. Discover vibrant coral reefs teeming with diverse marine life, from colorful fish to majestic manta rays. Dive into crystal-clear waters and experience the beauty of one of the world\'s most renowned diving destinations. This adventure awaits you beneath the waves!
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_kh1">
        Witness the incredible Komodo dragons, a must-see for visitors, which can be observed in their natural habitats at Loh Liang on Komodo Island and Loh Buaya on Rinca Island. These majestic creatures offer a glimpse into the primeval world, making the journey to these islands an unforgettable adventure for nature enthusiasts and wildlife photographers alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_kh2">
        Marvel at the red-footed booby, a fascinating bird that graces our shores with its vibrant plumage. This remarkable species finds solace in the coastal habitats, where it thrives. As the sun becomes higher, these beautiful birds gather, basking in the warm morning light, creating a mesmerizing spectacle for birdwatchers and nature enthusiasts alike.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_kh3">
        The park\'s beauty radiates through the presence of colorful and cheerful cockatoos. Their vibrant plumage paints the landscape with hues of pink, yellow, and white, creating a nice sight for visitors. The melodious chirping of these sociable birds adds a delightful soundtrack to the tranquil ambiance, enchanting all who wander through this natural sanctuary.
    </string>
    <string name="tn42_kh4">
        In the calm waters, watch the clownfish\'s playfulness in the enchanting coral reefs. Their vibrant hues dance amidst the swaying corals, a mesmerizing spectacle of nature\'s beauty. As they dart in and out of crevices, it\'s a glimpse into a world where harmony and grace reign supreme, inviting you to lose yourself in the serene underwater ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_a1">
        Escape the hustle and bustle of city life and immerse yourself in the serene beauty of Matalawa National Park. Wake up to the symphony of birdsong, breathe in the crisp, and fresh air at the majestic scenery surrounding you. Camping here offers a chance to reconnect with nature, rejuvenate your soul, and create unforgettable memories under the night sky.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_a2">
        Explore the captivating landscapes of Matalawa National Park, where every corner reveals breathtaking scenes of nature\'s splendor. From lush forests to cascading waterfalls, each moment is a masterpiece waiting to be revealed and captured. Immerse yourself in the astonishing diversity of flora and fauna and let the park\'s beauty inspire your senses.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_a3">
        Immerse yourself in the wonders of nature as you witness the vibrant wildlife and the captivating array of bird species that call this place home. From the graceful flight of eagles to the melodious chirping of songbirds, every moment spent here is a journey into the heart of biodiversity, offering an intricate tapestry of life thriving in this ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_kh1">
        Wake up to the symphony of exotic cockatoos gathering in Matalawa National Park, their vibrant plumage shimmering under the golden rays of dawn. Amidst the lush foliage, witness nature\'s spectacle unfold as these majestic birds herald the beginning of a new day with their enchanting calls, a scene that promises to etch itself into your memory forever.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_kh2">
        The rare Sumba hornbill, with its vibrant plumage and distinctive call, is just one of the many bird species that captivate the heart here. Its graceful flight across the verdant landscape adds to the enchantment of this tropical paradise, where biodiversity thrives, and every corner is alive with the melodious songs of nature\'s finest avian inhabitants.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_kh3">
        As the spotted kestrel gracefully glides through the azure expanse, its elegant flight becomes a symphony of beauty in the vast canvas of Matalawa National Park. Its presence, a testament to the rich biodiversity that thrives within this sanctuary, enchants visitors and locals alike, weaving a tapestry of wonder and admiration for the wonders of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_kh4">
        As you traverse through fields and forests, the enchanting Eulophia exelta orchid will grace your path with its vibrant hues. Its delicate petals dance in the gentle breeze, a testament to the beauty that thrives in the wild. Each bloom whispers tales of resilience and elegance, inviting everyone to immerse themself in the wonders of the natural world.
    </string>
    <string name="tn43_kh5">
        Nestled amidst the lush greenery of Matalawa National Park, the captivating Eulophia spectablis orchid enchants with its vibrant hues and intricate blooms. Each delicate petal tells a story of resilience and beauty, showcasing nature\'s remarkable artistry. Visitors are mesmerized by its elegance, a testament to the park\'s rich biodiversity and ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_a1">
        Discover the mesmerizing allure of Kalimutu National Park, where nature\'s splendor unfolds in breathtaking vistas. Encounter the enchanting hues of its iconic tri-colored lakes, a spectacle that transcends the ordinary. Immerse yourself in the tranquil ambiance of this natural wonder, where every moment is a testament to the earth\'s boundless magnificence.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_a2">
        Embark on an exhilarating journey through Kalimutu\'s stunning mountain ranges, immersing yourself in thrilling hiking adventures. Traverse the breathtaking peaks, witness nature\'s majesty unfolds before your eyes, and savor the serenity of the wilderness. Kalimutu promises unforgettable experiences amidst its awe-inspiring landscapes and awaits your visit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_a3">
        Immerse yourself in the vibrant tapestry of life and rich cultural heritage by engaging in an array of distinctive traditional activities found nowhere else. From intricate handicraft workshops to spirited folk dances, every experience promises to unveil the essence of local culture, fostering unforgettable memories that resonate long after your visit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_kh1">
        The Flores hawk-eagle, a majestic raptor, soars gracefully above the lush canopies of Kalimutu National Park, its distinctive silhouette adding to the park\'s biodiversity. Its presence underscores the park\'s status as a haven for rare and endangered species, highlighting the importance of conservation in preserving these majestic creatures and their habitat.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_kh2">
        The Garugiwa bird, renowned for its vivid feathers and harmonious tunes, enhances the verdant greenery of the national park with its presence. Its colorful feathers shimmer in the sunlight, captivating the eyes of all who visit the park. The melodious tunes it sings create a serene ambiance, making it a cherished symbol of the park\'s rich biodiversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn45_kh3">
        The lively and nimble monkeys, brimming with endless energy and playful charm, eagerly anticipate the arrival of visitors to the park, captivating them with their amusing antics and contagious delight. Their lively presence adds an extra layer of delight to the natural beauty of the park, creating unforgettable experiences for all who come to visit.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_a1">
        Experience the rush of adrenaline as you navigate turbulent waters with exhilarating white-water rafting. Feel the thrill of speed and adventure as you tackle challenging rapids, creating memories that will last a lifetime. Embark on an unforgettable journey down the river, where every twist and turn brings new excitement and unforgettable moments.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_a2">
        Embark on a journey to the summit of Mount Tambora, where awe-inspiring vistas await. Marvel at the panoramic views that stretch as far as the eye can see, immersing yourself in the natural beauty of this majestic peaks. Experience the thrill of conquering one of Indonesia\'s most iconic mountains while soaking in the tranquility of the surrounding landscape.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_a3">
        Feel the exhilarating rush of navigating rugged trails and conquering steep inclines on a motorcycle against the stunning backdrop of Mount Tambora. Experience the thrill of adventure as you traverse diverse terrains, from rocky paths to serpentine roads, immersing yourself in the unspoiled beauty of nature and indulging in adrenaline-charged exploits.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_kh1">
        Captivated by the Brahminy kite, its wings spread wide against the azure canvas of the Mount Tambora skies. Every swoop and glide paints a picture of freedom and majesty, commanding the heavens with effortless authority. Its presence, a testament to the untamed beauty of nature\'s realm, evokes a sense of wonder and admiration among all who gaze upon it.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_kh2">
        Embark on a journey through the lush forests of the national park, where the Flores hawk-eagle reigns supreme, its majestic form soaring through the azure skies. Amidst the verdant foliage, encounter a myriad of wildlife, from colorful avian species to elusive mammals, each contributing to the rich biodiversity that thrives in this pristine ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_kh3">
        As the sun dips low on the horizon, casting a warm glow across the landscape, the red-cheeked parrots take flight, their vibrant plumage a dazzling display against the canvas of the evening sky. With graceful arcs and playful chirps, they weave intricate patterns, painting the heavens with their kaleidoscope of colors, a mesmerizing spectacle for visitors.
    </string>
    <string name="tn46_kh4">
        Experience the enchantment of biodiversity as you embark on a journey to uncover the exquisite and rare Vanda Lombokensis orchid. Delight in its mesmerizing beauty and immerse yourself in the intricate wonders of nature\'s diversity. Venture into the heart of lush landscapes and discover the hidden treasures that await amidst the vibrant tapestry of life.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_a1">
        Experience the adrenaline rush as you navigate through the exhilarating rapids of the rivers in Aketajawe Lalobata National Park. Feel the thrill of conquering nature forces while surrounded by breathtaking landscapes. Whether you\'re a seasoned rafter or a beginner adventure, this park offers an unforgettable experience that will leave you craving for more.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_a2">
        Embark on thrilling journeys into the heart of Aketajawe Lalobata, where each step is a testament to exploration. Engage in daring outdoor pursuits that push the limits of adventure, from jungle treks to exhilarating water sports. Discover the untamed beauty of nature while embracing the spirit of adventure that defines this extraordinary destination.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_a3">
        Set off on thrilling treks to discover the captivating landscapes of Aketajawe-Lolobata. Navigate through dense forests, challenging terrains, and tumbling waterfalls. Allow the charm of the wilderness to enchant your senses as you delve into its magnificence. Feel the excitement of exploration as you uncover the secret wonders of this bewitching locale.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_kh1">
        Discover the vivid colors of the Halmahera paradise bird as it moves through the dense greenery of Aketajawe Lalobata National Park. Immerse yourself in the orchestra of natural colors, where every feather narrates a tale of extraordinary allure. Encounter the magic of this equatorial haven, where biodiversity flourishes and each turn reveals a fresh marvel.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_kh2">
        The Halmahera golden bulbul, with its vibrant plumage and melodious song, adds a touch of splendor to the rich tapestry of biodiversity within this national park. Its presence symbolizes the delicate balance of nature preserved within these pristine landscapes, captivating both researchers and nature enthusiasts alike with its elusive charm and beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_kh3">
        Emoia Kordoana, one of the small representatives of reptilian diversity in Aketajawe Lalobata National Park, dazzles with its vibrant scales. This diminutive creature, with its slender body and quick reflexes, navigates the lush foliage with ease. Its presence adds a layer of intrigue to the rich tapestry of wildlife thriving within the park\'s boundaries.
    </string>
    <string name="tn47_kh4">
        The distinctive call of Litoria Infrafrenata contributes to the remarkable amphibian diversity in this region. Amid the dense foliage, its melodic chirps add a captivating layer to the forest\'s natural symphony. The sight of its vivid green color merging flawlessly with the surroundings inspires a profound appreciation for the masterful artistry of nature.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_a1">
        Embrace the excitement of hiking through verdant forests to uncover the secluded splendor of Wayansela Waterfall within Manusela National Park. Allow the harmonious sounds of the falling water to refresh your soul while you take in the stunning scenery enveloping you. Stray from the well-trodden routes and delve into the marvels of the natural world allure.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_a2">
        Set off on a memorable expedition to scale Mount Binaiya within Manusela National Park, where each stride unveils breathtaking panoramas. Behold the splendor of nature from soaring elevations, an encounter beyond verbal description. Experience the surge of excitement as you climb, arriving at the pinnacle of adventure surrounded by extraordinary splendor.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_a3">
        Nestled in the heart of Manusela National Park, Ora Lodge offers a serene escape from the hustle and bustle of daily life. Immerse yourself in the untouched wilderness, where exotic wildlife awaits. Whether you\'re an adventurous explorer or seeking tranquility, Ora Lodge provides a perfect retreat. Experience unparalleled comfort amidst nature\'s splendors.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_a4">
        Experience extraordinary culture by enjoying the Cakalele Dance in Manusela National Park. The energetic movements of the dancers, accompanied by rhythmic beats, immerse you in centuries-old traditions. As they perform, captivating tales of the region\'s history and mythology unfold, leaving you spellbound and charmed by the richness of Indonesian culture.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_a5">
        Delve into the intricate web of life within the mangrove ecosystem of Manusela National Park and engage in immersive tracking activities that redefine the word beauty. Encounter captivating biodiverse, from elusive creatures to vibrant plant species. Experience the harmonious interplay of nature\'s elements amidst the serene backdrop of the mangrove forest.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_kh1">
        Manusela National Park dedication to biodiversity was shown in its promotion of the Moluccan Cockatoo, a symbol of the region\'s avian diversity. As visitors enter, they\'re greeted by vibrant depictions of native birds, underscoring the park\'s commitment to conservation and highlighting the importance of preserving habitats for these magnificent creatures.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_kh2">
        Discover the captivating beauty of Manusela National Park, where the enchanting cuscus thrives amidst lush greenery. Immerse yourself in the serene ambiance of this forest as you observe this charming creature in their natural habitat. Experience the harmony of nature as you witness the cuscus in action, a truly mesmerizing sight that will leave you in awe.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_kh3">
        Their vibrant plumage and playful antics enchant visitors, offering a glimpse into the park\'s rich ecology. As they flit among the canopy, their presence underscores the delicate balance of the ecosystem. Each chirp and flutter add to the symphony of life, reminding us of our responsibility to preserve this natural treasure for generations to come.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_kh4">
        In the verdant expanse of Manusela National Park, the presence of Bulbophyllum sp enriches its biodiversity tapestry, evoking awe with its rarity. These natural marvels, flourishing in hidden enclaves, capture the essence of the park\'s beauty, highlighting the vital importance of conservation initiatives to safeguard these treasures for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn48_kh5">
        Explore the enchanting allure of Thelasis sp, nestled within the lush landscapes of Manusela National Park. These exquisite plants epitomize the park\'s extraordinary biodiversity, captivating visitors with their unique charm. Immerse yourself in the splendor of nature\'s bounty as you behold these wonders, a testament to the park\'s rich ecological heritage.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_a1">
        Step into the national park and experience the adventure in Cenderawasih Bay. Dive into crystal-clear waters teeming with vibrant marine life, encounter majestic whale sharks, and explore lush rainforests brimming with exotic flora and fauna. Whether you\'re an avid diver or a nature enthusiast, this breathtaking destination offers unparalleled experiences.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_a2">
        Plunge fearlessly into the azure depths and unlock the secrets of the mesmerizing underwater wonderland in Cenderawasih Bay, nestled within the expansive Teluk Cenderawasih National Park. Explore vibrant coral reefs, encounter majestic marine creatures, and fully immerse yourself in the rich and enchanting marine biodiversity of this tropical paradise.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_a3">
        Immerse yourself in the vibrant tapestry of culture and tradition nestled within the pristine landscapes of Cenderawasih National Park. From native rituals to local cuisine, each aspect of this alluring destination offers a window into the rich culture of the region, inviting visitors to embark on a journey of discovery amidst its amazing natural beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_kh1">
        In the lush, verdant tropical forests of Barawai, male Birds of Paradise put on mesmerizing displays of vibrant wing flaps and intricate tail dances, all in a spectacular effort to court their potential mates. This enchanting ritual, eagerly witnessed by fortunate tourists, showcases the breathtaking beauty and natural wonder of Barawai\'s wildlife.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_kh2">
        Witness the awe-inspiring sight of whale sharks adroitly swimming in Cenderawasih Bay\'s pristine waters. Seeing these majestic creatures in their habitat offers a rare moment to enjoy their calm demeanor and impressive size up close. Swimming alongside them is a humbling encounter, showcasing the curious marine life diversity and beauty of Cenderawasih Bay.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_kh3">
        Green turtles spend their lives in the sea, but during nesting season (June to September), females return to Cenderawasih Bay\'s shores. During the nesting season (June to September), female green turtles return to Cenderawasih Bay\'s shores to lay their eggs. They dig nests in the sand, carefully laying and covering their eggs before returning to the sea.
    </string>
    <string name="tn49_kh4">
        Experience the fresh beauty of clownfish in Cenderawasih Bay\'s clear waters. These vibrant fish, with their distinctive orange and white stripes, create a charming display against the backdrop of colorful coral reefs. Witness the riveting beauty of clownfish in Cenderawasih Bay, observing their unique behavior and symbiotic relationship with sea anemones.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_a1">
        Embark on a frantic adventure in an alluring snowy landscape, where crisp air and sparkling snow energize your senses. Cross serene terrain, ringed by snow-capped mountains and a magical atmosphere. The crunch of snow underfoot and icicles create a winter wonderland. Whether skiing or enjoying the serenity, this cold adventure offers a memorable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_a2">
        Conquer Lorentz National Park\'s majestic peaks for an extraordinary achievement. As you climb, the landscape transforms, revealing breathtaking wilderness views. Each step pushes your limits, a testament to your determination. At the summit, the world unfolds in a stunning panorama, a reward for your journey, evoking a profound sense of accomplishment.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_a3">
        Immerse yourself in Lorentz\'s cultural tapestry, featuring local customs, music, dance, and art that reflect the diverse heritage of its people. From traditional ceremonies to crafts, each aspect offers a glimpse into the rich history and traditions of the region. Lorentz\'s culture, whether ancient rituals or modern celebrations, leaves a lasting impression.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_kh1">
        Lucky to spot the rare black bear in Lorentz National Park, a thrilling moment showcasing its biodiversity. These elusive black bears, known for their distinctive fur and shy nature, roam the park\'s dense forests, adding to its allure. The presence of these majestic animals underscores the importance of conserving their habitat for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_kh2">
        Witness the beauty of hummingbirds in Lorentz National Park, where they dart among the flowers with astonishing agility. Observing these remarkable creatures provides insight into their relationship with the floral landscape. Their presence in Lorentz National Park underscores the critical and urgent need to preserve its biodiversity for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_kh3">
        The rare discovery of Goura scheepmakeri, or the Scheepmaker\'s crowned pigeon, in Lorentz National Park is a momentous event. This stunning bird is renowned for its beauty and regal presence, highlighting the park\'s biodiversity and pristine wilderness. Witnessing this majestic bird offers a glimpse into the preserved wonders of Lorentz National Park.
    </string>
    <string name="tn50_kh4">
        Various duck species, with colorful plumage and graceful movements, adorn the rivers and lakes of Lorentz National Park, enhancing its natural beauty. Against the backdrop of lush forests and towering mountains, these waterfowl create a serene scene. Observing them offers a glimpse into the park\'s rich avian diversity and their role in the ecosystem.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_a1">
        Embark on a thrilling biking adventure in Wasur National Park. Pedal along rugged trails and winding paths to immerse yourself in nature\'s untouched beauty. The park\'s diverse landscapes offer an ideal backdrop for an exhilarating ride. Whether you seek an adrenaline rush or to connect with nature, biking in Wasur promises an unforgettable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_a2">
        Witness the beauty of traditional Marori ceremonies, deeply intertwined with their natural surroundings and ancestral heritage. These ceremonies showcase the tribe\'s resilience and uncommon identity, reflecting their spiritual beliefs and social structure. By observing, you will get insight into the values that have sustained the Marori for centuries.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_a3">
      Experience the captivating \'men-gey\' tradition of the Marori tribe in Wasur, rooted in their heritage, showcasing unique customs, dances, and music. Participating or observing \'men-gey\' offers a glimpse into the rich cultural tapestry of the Marori, highlighting their connection to the land and ancestral traditions, enriching understanding of Marori culture.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_kh1">
        The colorful birds of paradise enhance the Wasur National Park experience. Their vibrant plumage and courtship displays are a true spectacle. Observing them in their natural habitat treats visitors to dazzling colors and behaviors, showcasing the park\'s rich biodiversity. Their presence underscores Wasur\'s importance as a haven for stunning avian species.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_kh2">
        Cheerful and colorful cockatoos are one of Wasur National Park\'s many charms. These vibrant birds, with striking plumage and playful behavior, enliven the park\'s diverse ecosystem. Visitors are captivated by their sight and sound, showcasing the area\'s rich biodiversity and beauty. The cockatoos\' bright feathers and cheerful calls make every visit eventful.
    </string>
    <string name="tn51_kh3">
       The cassowary, a unique bird, enriches the biodiversity of Wasur with its presence. This remarkable creature, with its striking appearance and important ecological role, is proof of the richness and diversity of Wasur\'s ecosystem. Its presence highlights the importance of conservation efforts to protect the natural ancestry of this particular region.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_a1">
       Embark on an exciting river cruise in Zamrud National Park, where each turn unveils new natural wonders. Glide through the water, ringed by lush greenery, and feel a sense of calm and awe. Observe wildlife in their natural habitat and appreciate Zamrud\'s pristine wilderness. Whether seeking peace or adventure, a river cruise here promises enduring memories.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_a2">
Experience the thrill of a high-speed journey aboard a speedboat in Zamrud National Park. As you zip across the water, the wind rushing past you, you\'ll feel a sense of exhilaration and freedom. The speedboat ride offers an extraordinary and exciting way to experience Zamrud National Park, whether admiring lush riverbank greenery or spotting wildlife.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_a3">
 Experience the elation of a speedboat ride through Zamrud\'s peat swamp forest. Glide along the water, ringed by lush greenery, for a rare context of the vast, natural beauty. Hear the forest\'s sounds and feel the cool breeze, creating enduring memories of Zamrud\'s wonders and the patience of its untouched outback, an exploit that will stay with you forever.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_kh1">
       Witness the melodious siamangs in Zamrud National Park, known for their haunting calls. These primates swing effortlessly through trees, their long, agile arms darting them with grace. As you watch, you\'ll be engaged by their social interactions and family dynamics. Zamrud National Park offers a rare hope to witness these creatures, showing control concern.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_kh2">
        Explore the rich biodiversity of Zamrud by encountering the rare pitcher plants, unique botanical wonders that add to the area\'s allure and reveal the depth of its ecological treasures. These plants, with their distinctive pitcher-shaped leaves, showcase Zamrud\'s diverse and alluring plant life, highlighting its unique and ecologically important ecosystems.
    </string>
    <string name="tn52_kh3">
      Embark on a thrilling birdwatching adventure in the wilds of Zamrud and witness a diverse array of bird species, including the majestic White Crested Laughingthrush. Zamrud\'s lush and varied landscapes provide a perfect habitat for these birds, offering a fascinating glimpse into their natural behaviors and interactions in a pristine, natural setting.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_a1">
        Experience a challenging hiking adventure in Gandang Dwata National Park, with rugged trails leading through diverse landscapes, rewarding you with breathtaking views and a sense of accomplishment. Bathe yourself in the beauty of nature at Gandang Dwata National Park, where the symphony of wildlife and the bracing mountain air combine to refresh your senses.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_a2">
     Discover Gandang Dwata\'s beauty, dropping yourself in its stunning view, vibrant flora, and diverse wildlife. Marvel at Gandang Dwata\'s lush landscapes, vibrant flora, and diverse fauna, where every corner—from hilltop vistas to serene forests and colorful wildflowers—promises enduring moments. Let Gandang Dwata\'s alluring ambience inspire and renew you.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_a3">
        Explore Gandang Dwata\'s rich environment, encountering playful monkeys, colorful birds, elusive reptiles, and bustling insects. Crystal-clear streams teem with life, offering a glimpse of the underwater world. Whether a wildlife enthusiast or nature lover, Gandang Dwata promises an unforgettable experience with fascinating creatures at every corner.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_kh1">
      Explore Gandang Dwata\'s diverse wildlife, from playful monkeys to colorful birds, elusive reptiles, and bustling insects, all in lush surroundings. Crystal-clear streams teem with life, offering a glimpse into an underwater world. Whether a wildlife fan or nature lover, Gandang Dwata owes an enduring experience, with fascinating creatures in every corner.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_kh2">
Explore the diverse mushrooms of Gandang Dwata, from tiny fungi on the forest floor to majestic varieties on fallen logs. Seek the forest\'s array of shapes, sizes, and colors, each showcasing nature beauty. Gandang Dwata\'s mushroom diversity efforts its rich ecosystem. Whether you\'re a mycology fan or nature lover, this visit will awe you with its diversity.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_kh3">
Seek the baffling lichen forest in Gandang Dwata, where branches draped in lichen create an ethereal atmosphere. Wander through this unique ecosystem, surrounded by the beauty of lichen thriving in clean, unpolluted air. The forest is a haven for biodiversity, providing a habitat for insects and small animals, offering an mesmeric, awe-inspiring experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn53_kh4">
    Seek rare and unique plants in Gandang Dwata, a botanical paradise with varied flora. Wander through lush gardens, evading an amazing array of colors and shapes. Gandang Dwata is a living laboratory for scientists studying these notable plants. Whether you\'re a botany enthusiast or simply appreciate nature\'s beauty, a visit owes a memorable experience.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_a1">
     See a variety of bird species in Mount Maras. The mountain\'s diverse habitat, from dense forests to open grasslands, hosts a wide array of bird species. Birdwatchers will enjoy spotting both common and rare species, adding to the allure of this natural haven. Whether you\'re a bird fan or just love birds, Mount Maras will captivate you with its wonders.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_a2">
        Embark on an adventure along a beautiful, flowing river amidst Mount Maras. The river\'s crystal-clear waters wind through the lush greenery, creating a serene and picturesque setting. Along the way, you may spot various wildlife species that call the riverbank home, adding to the sense of wonder and excitement.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_a3">
       Marvel at the stunning view from Bukit Nenek, one of the natural attractions of Mount Maras. The look offers a panoramic vista of lush greenery stretching as far as the eye can see, with occasional glimpses of exotic wildlife.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_kh1">
        Encounter amazing wildlife, including macaques, in Mount Maras. These creatures roam freely in lush foliage, adding to the allure of this natural paradise. While hiking, you might see macaques swinging from trees, adding joy and showcasing Mount Maras\'s biodiversity. These encounters underscore the need to preserve such environments for future generations.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_kh2">
      Sumatran elephants, majestic creatures, are the guardians of Mount Maras\' biodiversity. Their presence is a testament to the rich ecosystem that thrives in this mountainous region. These gentle giants play a crucial role in maintaining the balance of the ecosystem, their movements shaping the landscape in ways that benefit the flora and fauna around them.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_kh3">
        As you cross the mountain\'s trails, you may spot these elegant creatures grazing peacefully in the meadows or wandering through the dense forests. The sambar deer, with its majestic antlers and sleek coat, adds to the natural charm of Mount Maras. Their presence, along with other wildlife sightings, enhances the experience of exploring this biodiverse haven.
    </string>
    <string name="tn54_kh4">
      Mount Maras is a treasure trove of natural wonders, boasting the rare and breathtaking Rafflesia flowers. These remarkable blooms, with their enormous, captivating petals, are a sight to behold, adding bursts of vibrant color to the lush green landscape. The mountain\'s serene ambiance enhances the experience, creating a calm retreat for nature enthusiasts.
    </string>
    <string name="ganti_bahasa">Language changed to English</string>
    <string name="klik_disini">Click here</string>
    <string name="info_lanjut">For more information</string>
    <string name="download_app">Download Indonesia\'s FOLU Net Sink 2030 Application</string>
    <string name="pindai_target">Scan Target to show AR</string>
    <string name="pulau_sumatra">Sumatra \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_sulawesi">Sulawesi \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_papua">Papua \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_maluku">Maluku \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_kalimantan">Kalimantan \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_jawa">Jawa \nIsland</string>
    <string name="pulau_bali">Lesser Sunda \nIslands</string>
    <string name="klhk">KLHK</string>
    <string name="kembali">Back</string>
</resources>